好的，我们将继续完成
all right so we're going to continue to finish up
so we're going to continue to finish up lecture 2 with a few basic definitions
第2课有一些基本定义，然后讨论了这种分离
lecture 2 with a few basic definitions and then discussed about this separation
and then discussed about this separation which is sort of the most rigorous and
这是获得独立的最严格和最简单的方法
which is sort of the most rigorous and easiest way to take independence
easiest way to take independence relations from on directed and
定向和非定向工作之间的关系，所以让我们来谈谈一些
relations from on directed and undirected jobs so let's pick up a few
undirected jobs so let's pick up a few slides from lecture two so this is an
第二讲的幻灯片，这是一个例子，但我的意思是我希望你能拿十个
slides from lecture two so this is an example but I mean I hope you take ten
example but I mean I hope you take ten minutes for somebody to type this
分钟，以便有人正确输入此方程式，这意味着我希望我
minutes for somebody to type this equation right which means I expect me
equation right which means I expect me to at least spend ten minutes to
至少要花十分钟到一分钟
to at least spend ten minutes to actually a minute
actually a minute okay and it looks awful for everything
好的，对于所有琐碎的事看起来都很糟糕，但是有很多实质内容
okay and it looks awful for everything trivial but there's a lot of substance
trivial but there's a lot of substance in terms of calculation so I'm going to
在计算方面，所以我将在课程中的任何地方继续进行，所以我
in terms of calculation so I'm going to carry on everywhere in the course so I
carry on everywhere in the course so I wanted to go through this example in a
想详细了解此示例，也许您知道花了一个
wanted to go through this example in a few more details maybe you know spend a
few more details maybe you know spend a minute or two so this note is not about
一两分钟，因此此注释与性别无关-x3表示该属性将
minute or two so this note is not about sex - x3 indicate and this belong will
sex - x3 indicate and this belong will be the case today in the course indicate
今天在课程中的情况是表明证据，所以我们已经观察到了这个想法
be the case today in the course indicate evidence so the idea is we have observed
evidence so the idea is we have observed next to X 3 that's quite a mark okay and
X 3旁边的标记是可以的，如果我们有的话，我们想证明这一点
next to X 3 that's quite a mark okay and what we want to prove this if we have
what we want to prove this if we have observed exponent 3 X 1 and X 6 are
观察到的指数3 X 1和X 6是独立的，所以这
observed exponent 3 X 1 and X 6 are independent okay so this but the
independent okay so this but the notation rates
记号率，因此再次获得了极限国歌
notation rates so again explore extreme anthems by got
so again explore extreme anthems by got some evidence and I want to know now are
一些证据，我现在想知道X 1和X 6的普遍性
some evidence and I want to know now are given the prevalence of X 1 and X 6
given the prevalence of X 1 and X 6 independent okay so effectively what we
独立好吧，所以我们需要有效地证明是，所以我们需要X 2和X 3
independent okay so effectively what we need to prove is so we need X 2 and X 3
need to prove is so we need X 2 and X 3 different so we need to prove now the
不同，所以我们现在需要证明给定X 1 X 2的火柴杆概率
different so we need to prove now the probability of matchsticks given X 1 X 2
probability of matchsticks given X 1 X 2 X 3 it's equal to the probability of
X 3等于以其他方式给定X 2 X 3的极端概率为
X 3 it's equal to the probability of extreme given X 2 X 3 in other way is
extreme given X 2 X 3 in other way is knowing this evidence the information of
知道这一证据后，X 1的信息就不会出售，这使您对X 6有所了解
knowing this evidence the information of X 1 doesn't sell making you about X 6
X 1 doesn't sell making you about X 6 okay
好吧，显然这是蛮力的
okay and obviously this brute
and obviously this brute the long way but this is what we are at
很长的路要走，但这是我们目前所处的方向，所以在哪里
the long way but this is what we are at the course at this point ok so where the
the course at this point ok so where the headband is I noticed as the joint in
我注意到头带，因为分子中的联合是联合概率
headband is I noticed as the joint in the numerator is the joint probability
the numerator is the joint probability of X 1 X 2 X 3 and X 6 which means this
X 1 X 2 X 3和X 6的乘积，这是两极化的总联合概率
of X 1 X 2 X 3 and X 6 which means this is the total joint probability polarized
is the total joint probability polarized on the graph and then obviously have to
在图表上，然后显然必须整合X 4和X 5的方式
on the graph and then obviously have to integrate how's X 4 and X 5 all right
integrate how's X 4 and X 5 all right and then in the denominator have the
然后在分母中有X 1 X 2 X 3的连接
and then in the denominator have the joining of X 1 X 2 X 3 which means I
joining of X 1 X 2 X 3 which means I have to integrate out X 4 X 5 and X 6
必须整合X 4 X 5和X 6好的算法的重要意义
have to integrate out X 4 X 5 and X 6 okay the important thing that algorithm
okay the important thing that algorithm that is going to save us when we work
当我们通过这种类型的图工作时，这将拯救我们的是
that is going to save us when we work through this type of graphs is that we
through this type of graphs is that we can put some of these summations in
可以用词来表示这些总和中的一些，例如，您有总和
can put some of these summations in words so for example you have summation
words so for example you have summation X 5 and the only terms that depends
X 5和唯一依赖于区域X 5或上一个术语的术语，因此您
X 5 and the only terms that depends region X 5 or goes to last term so you
region X 5 or goes to last term so you can put X 5 the situation at this point
可以在此时将X 5的情况放好，然后将X中的目的地
can put X 5 the situation at this point okay and then the destination in X for
okay and then the destination in X for this x don't depend on exposure you can
这个x不依赖于曝光，您可以在此处推送目的地，但不可以
this x don't depend on exposure you can push destination in here but not you
push destination in here but not you know notice there is an X 2 there right
知道注意那里有一个X 2，它将成为目的地的一部分
know notice there is an X 2 there right and and that will be part of destination
and and that will be part of destination that after forming expired all right so
那形成后就没事了，所以总和是X 5人，然后在
that after forming expired all right so the summation is person X 5 then in
the summation is person X 5 then in export and similarly in the denominator
导出，并且在分母中类似地是X 6和X 5的总和，然后导出
export and similarly in the denominator is the summation X 6 and X 5 then export
is the summation X 6 and X 5 then export it's important to this is sort of the
这很重要，这是允许使用的主要技巧
it's important to this is sort of the main trick use to allow
main trick use to allow rocking inconsistent overly structured
摇摆不一致的过度结构化的水调制的五角星。
rocking inconsistent overly structured water a pentacle for modulation for the
water a pentacle for modulation for the same time good luck okay alright so a
同时祝你好运好吧，所以很多事情都取消了，所以这可能
same time good luck okay alright so a lot of the things cancel out so this may
lot of the things cancel out so this may because this is a condition distribution
因为这是条件分布蒸馏
because this is a condition distribution distillation
distillation becomes equal to 1 regardless what
变得等于1而不管外部是什么，所以这个和这个抵消了
becomes equal to 1 regardless what exteriors so this and this cancel out so
exteriors so this and this cancel out so basically I'm sorry business and cancel
基本上我很抱歉，取消此等价等于1等于
basically I'm sorry business and cancel out this cut is equal to 1 this is equal
out this cut is equal to 1 this is equal to 1 so basically this illustris allow
到1，所以基本上，这个illustris允许
to 1 so basically this illustris allow this
you know it's one anyways so I get this big donation on the numerator which is
你知道那是一个，所以我在分子上得到了大笔捐款
big donation on the numerator which is this and then there's somebody pointed
这然后有人指向我，只是他们会他来见我，他
this and then there's somebody pointed me just they would he came to see me he
me just they would he came to see me he says to me why is this equal to laughs
对我说为什么这等于笑，因为你突然发现我插上电源
says to me why is this equal to laughs because you notice suddenly I plug in
because you notice suddenly I plug in Ian's in addition to extreme x2 and in
Ian除了极限x2和额外的x5外，我还插入了
Ian's in addition to extreme x2 and in addition to extra x5 I plug in an
addition to extra x5 I plug in an extreme white house
极端的白宫
所以在这里，我有X 5给定X 3 X 5给定X 3，然后我可以，但这等于
addition to extra x5 I plug in an extreme white house
so here I have X 5 given X 3 X 5 given X 3 and then I could but this is equal to
所以在这里，我有X 5给定X 3 X 5给定X 3，然后我可以，但这等于
3 and then I could but this is equal to X 5 and X 3 and X 2 what property from
X 5和X 3和X 2从我们说的父母那里得到什么财产，不，我没有看到
X 5 and X 3 and X 2 what property from the ones we say parent no I don't see a
the ones we say parent no I don't see a parent X 2 is not the power
父X 2不是力量
是的，但是我们所说的基本独立属性之一
the ones we say parent no I don't see a parent X 2 is not the power
yeah but one of the fundamental independent properties that we stated
是的，但是我们所说的基本独立属性之一
independent properties that we stated and we will see three times today or
我们今天将看到三遍，或者四遍是给定父节点的节点
and we will see three times today or four is the given the parent the node is
four is the given the parent the node is independent of of the non-descendants
再次独立于非后裔，不公正的无后裔
independent of of the non-descendants again the no descendants of the unjust
again the no descendants of the unjust was basically plus some extra notes okay
基本上加上一些额外的注释就可以了，所以在这种情况下X 2不是祖先
was basically plus some extra notes okay so in this case X 2 is not an ancestor
so in this case X 2 is not an ancestor is a lone dissenter because the only
是唯一的异议者，因为X 5的唯一访问权是X 3和X 1 all
is a lone dissenter because the only access third of X 5 is X 3 and X 1 all
access third of X 5 is X 3 and X 1 all right
正确的x2是非后代，所以在其他方面
right x2 is a non descendant so in other ways
x2 is a non descendant so in other ways you can see the arrows you can go from 5
您可以看到箭头，您可以从5转到6
you can see the arrows you can go from 5 to 6
to 6 you know what to do so XQ is a non
你知道该怎么做，所以XQ是非后代，好了，再次，我们将看到这个
you know what to do so XQ is a non descender ok so again we will see this
descender ok so again we will see this property together but given the power
在一起，但给定幂和X 3，则X 5的概率为
property together but given the power and X 3 this the probability of X 5 is
and X 3 this the probability of X 5 is independent X 5 is independent of the
独立X 5独立于非依赖X且类似地依赖于
independent X 5 is independent of the non depends on X and similarly on the
non depends on X and similarly on the second probability I plug in what I can
第二个可能性是我在这里插入3我给定的X 2和X 5 2和5
second probability I plug in what I can here 3 so given X 2 and X 5 2 and 5
here 3 so given X 2 and X 5 2 and 5 which are the parents of extinct I plug
这是我灭绝的父母，我插入了3，而3是你所知道的
which are the parents of extinct I plug in 3 and 3 is a what it's a you know
in 3 and 3 is a what it's a you know it's obviously not descendant but it you
这显然不是后裔，但你知道这基本上是祖父母50
it's obviously not descendant but it you know it's a grandparent basically 50
know it's a grandparent basically 50 okay it's an ancestor of lectures okay
好吧，这是讲座的祖先，好吧，因为我必须插入这个
okay it's an ancestor of lectures okay so in the reason I have to plug in this
so in the reason I have to plug in this time start is because these two
时间开始是因为这两个分布一起给了我
time start is because these two distributions together they give me the
distributions together they give me the probability of X 5 and X 6 condition X 2
X 5和X 6条件X 2 X 3的概率，如果我将X 5完全积分
probability of X 5 and X 6 condition X 2 X 3 and if I integrate X 5 altogether
X 3 and if I integrate X 5 altogether from Reliford 6 given X 2 X 3 and then
从Reliford 6得到X 2 X 3，那么这个身份就可以了
from Reliford 6 given X 2 X 3 and then this identity has been put okay
this identity has been put okay so this way when tisha here at work is a
因此，当tisha在这里工作时，这是很多重要的小事情
so this way when tisha here at work is a lot of little things that are important
lot of little things that are important basically when you work with high
基本上，当您使用高维分布时，很明显
basically when you work with high dimensional distributions so obviously
dimensional distributions so obviously we use the factorization of this
我们使用图的这种分布的因式分解，我们设法
we use the factorization of this distribution of the graph we managed to
distribution of the graph we managed to do some of the optimizations by
通过适当地删除站点中的站点来进行一些优化
do some of the optimizations by appropriately removing the stations in
appropriately removing the stations in words okay starting basically from the
可以的话基本上是从Leafs的基础开始，然后最终
words okay starting basically from the Leafs base and then eventually going to
Leafs base and then eventually going to the to the root as needed and then we
根据需要到根，然后我们在这里使用独立关系
the to the root as needed and then we use the independence relation here of
use the independence relation here of the parent overall being given the parts
父母整体被赋予独立的部分，没有后代；
the parent overall being given the parts being independent no descendants and
being independent no descendants and that's it okay so let me we discuss this
没关系，所以让我讨论这个例子，但我想回到它后面，
that's it okay so let me we discuss this example but I want to go back to it and
example but I want to go back to it and then we will do this with again with the
然后我们将再次使用蒸馏算法进行此操作，因此我们有一个案例
then we will do this with again with the distillation algorithm so we have a case
distillation algorithm so we have a case here over wet grass sprinkler being on
这里的湿草喷头总体上上下雨，所以基本上这些
here over wet grass sprinkler being on or off rain overall so basically these
or off rain overall so basically these are binary variables okay and you can
是二进制变量，可以看到各种问题之一
are binary variables okay and you can see various problems one the goes from
see various problems one the goes from causes to effects such as cloudy this
导致诸如多云的影响，这将导致下雨，这将导致
causes to effects such as cloudy this will cause rain and this will cause to
will cause rain and this will cause to say the glass will be wet so far forward
说玻璃会被弄湿，到目前为止B中的推断问题是玻璃
say the glass will be wet so far forward inference problems in B is the glass
inference problems in B is the glass weren't given that's cloudy
没有得到多云的消息，因此来自
weren't given that's cloudy right so information from a gates in the
right so information from a gates in the direction of the graph all right so this
图的方向很好，所以这是从正x开始的，那就是
direction of the graph all right so this is from positive x and that's the
is from positive x and that's the problem
好吧，这是一个非常简单的问题
all right so that's a very easy problem this is very similar sort of to what you
这与您在贝叶斯统计中所做的非常相似
this is very similar sort of to what you do in Bayesian statistics will be likely
do in Bayesian statistics will be likely to write if you know the parameters what
写，如果你知道参数是什么输出，所以这会导致
to write if you know the parameters what is the output so here this causes the
is the output so here this causes the grass to be red so you're asking what is
草是红色的，所以您要问的是，续集等于1
grass to be red so you're asking what is will become equal 1 given to the sequel
will become equal 1 given to the sequel to the more important problem is the
最重要的问题是去工厂的英语问题
to the more important problem is the English problem to go for the factory
English problem to go for the factory closes so if the grass is wet somebody
关闭，这样如果草是湿的，有人可以说是在下雨吗
closes so if the grass is wet somebody can say is it raining in other words if
can say is it raining in other words if W is equal to R is R equal to R what's
W等于R等于R等于R L的概率更重要
W is equal to R is R equal to R what's the probability of L even more important
the probability of L even more important questions if the grass is wet is the
问题是草是否潮湿是排水口高于
questions if the grass is wet is the probability that the drain higher than
probability that the drain higher than the probability that the sprinkler
洒水效果还可以的概率
the probability that the sprinkler result okay
好吧，实际上这和我在这里的有点不同
well actually that's a little bit different from from the one I have here
different from from the one I have here but basically seen in the same spirit
但基本上是本着相同的精神，我们将在更多内容中看到
but basically seen in the same spirit and something that we will see in more
and something that we will see in more detail in the lecture today is this in a
今天讲课的细节是在池塘里的，所以让我们仔细地看一看。
detail in the lecture today is this in a pond so let's look at it again carefully
pond so let's look at it again carefully because we went through it but you know
因为我们经历了它，但是您知道您应该如何开始参加此活动
because we went through it but you know what should you start getting this event
what should you start getting this event if you sleep ten times in the slide so I
如果您在幻灯片中睡了十次，那么我必须确定两个概率
if you sleep ten times in the slide so I have to condition probabilities both of
have to condition probabilities both of them stray or conditional on the grass
他们在草地上流浪或有条件地被弄湿，等于我的两倍。
them stray or conditional on the grass being wet double equal to one and what I
being wet double equal to one and what I try to infer is if the sprinkler is on
尝试推断是洒水器是打开还是关闭，以及此处的参数是否为
try to infer is if the sprinkler is on or off and the argument here if this
or off and the argument here if this equation is correct I say given the
等式是正确的，我说给定伤害等于一，我说如果我也
equation is correct I say given the damage equals one I say that if I also
damage equals one I say that if I also know that it's rain this probability is
知道下雨了，这个可能性不大涉及，所以我想让你
know that it's rain this probability is less involved all right so I want you to
less involved all right so I want you to look at this equation carefully because
仔细看一下这个方程，因为他们洒水和下雨是什么
look at this equation carefully because what the sprinkler and the rain they
what the sprinkler and the rain they cause the glass to be wet so if somehow
导致玻璃被弄湿，所以如果有某种原因，这是证据，如果您有
cause the glass to be wet so if somehow so with this is an evidence if you have
so with this is an evidence if you have some information that they play this
他们播放的一些信息立即降低了
some information that they play this immediately reduces the probabilities of
immediately reduces the probabilities of the sprinkler result because this
洒水器的结果，因为这一证据
the sprinkler result because this evidence
evidence the grass is wet right so you have two
草是湿的，所以这里有两个可能的原因
the grass is wet right so you have two possible causes here that the grass is
possible causes here that the grass is wet and if this was not there at all
湿的，如果根本不存在，那么我们没有更低的
wet and if this was not there at all right so we didn't have any the lower
right so we didn't have any the lower part of the graph is the probability of
图的一部分是洒水的概率是洒水的排水量
part of the graph is the probability of the sprinkler is the sprinkler drain
the sprinkler is the sprinkler drain independent of each other
如果没有连接间距，则彼此独立
independent of each other if there is no no connection spacing you
if there is no no connection spacing you just have the sprinkler and Lorraine are
只是有洒水器和洛林他们是独立的
just have the sprinkler and Lorraine are they independent
they independent all right if they're independent now
如果它们独立，现在就可以了，一旦您观察到气体就可以了
all right if they're independent now once you observe the gas all right
once you observe the gas all right that's on vacation they are not
那是在度假，他们不是独立的权利，因为知道
that's on vacation they are not independent right because knowing that
independent right because knowing that something about if it rained or not
关于是否下雨的一些信息立即告诉您有关它的一些信息
something about if it rained or not immediately tells you something about it
immediately tells you something about it the sprinkler is all about so this is a
洒水器的作用就在于此，这是一个奇怪的事件，它只出现在
the sprinkler is all about so this is a weird event that it only appears in
weird event that it only appears in directional graphs and it is going to
有向图，它将改变许多名称，这说明了
directional graphs and it is going to vary many names explaining away is the
vary many names explaining away is the most common sense name right so
最常识的名称正确，所以观察其中的原因之一
most common sense name right so observing one of the causes that the
observing one of the causes that the grass is wet it explains the way in the
草是湿的，它说明了洒水效果还可以的方式
grass is wet it explains the way in the fact that the sprinkler result okay sort
fact that the sprinkler result okay sort of a concept that doesn't come in other
在其他类型的图（例如在X无向下）中不会出现的概念
of a concept that doesn't come in other sorts of graphs like under X undirected
sorts of graphs like under X undirected jobs
职位
好吧，我个人还有其他问题，您可以解决。
sorts of graphs like under X undirected jobs
okay I personally have some additional questions you can work them out okay and
好吧，我个人还有其他问题，您可以解决。
questions you can work them out okay and the same way is the first example that I
同样的方式是我今天向您展示的第一个示例，因此使用
the same way is the first example that I showed you today so using which
showed you today so using which marginalization and moving the
边际化和用词移动总和，所以我要
marginalization and moving the summations in words so I'm going to
summations in words so I'm going to repeat this example shortly the local
简短地重复此示例，我们拥有的本地属性微观属性
repeat this example shortly the local property micro property that we have
property micro property that we have used them and I will try to give you
用过它们，我会尽力为您提供形状各异的阻力
used them and I will try to give you well shapes different resistance of this
well shapes different resistance of this is that given the parts of a node V xB
是给定节点V xB的部分独立于
is that given the parts of a node V xB is independent of the non descendents of
is independent of the non descendents of the node V and I am generalizing here
V节点，我在这里概括，我并不是说必须是父母的
the node V and I am generalizing here I'm not saying have to be of the parents
I'm not saying have to be of the parents of V I mean I'm not saying of the
VI的意思是我不是说am的祖先，而是说
of V I mean I'm not saying of the ancestors of the am saying the
ancestors of the am saying the non-descendants
非后裔，那更大的人没有压力
non-descendants which that is bigger the unstressed
which that is bigger the unstressed orthogonal descendants
正交子孙
哪个类型的祖先越强，后裔越强
which that is bigger the unstressed orthogonal descendants
which type is bigger the ancestral stronger non-descendants the
哪个类型的祖先越强，后裔越强
stronger non-descendants the non-descendants is bigger right so I can
非子孙后代的权利更大，所以我可以写这个，我也可以
non-descendants is bigger right so I can write this also I can take a subset of
write this also I can take a subset of anyway which are the ancestors and text
无论如何，祖先和我发的短信都独立于给定的祖先
anyway which are the ancestors and text me is independent of the ancestors given
me is independent of the ancestors given the part and I want you to think if you
该部分，我想让您考虑一下是否要对拓扑进行排序
the part and I want you to think if you have a topological ordering the
have a topological ordering the ancestors basically are the notes that
祖先基本上是在我们当权之前编号的音符
ancestors basically are the notes that are numbered before we in the authority
are numbered before we in the authority but the non-descendants they have
但是非后裔的数字都高于C
but the non-descendants they have numbers that they're higher than C all
numbers that they're higher than C all right it's important here the
对，在这里重要的是你的后裔数字
right it's important here the non-descendants you have numbers that
non-descendants you have numbers that have higher than this okay
比这个还高[鼓掌]
have higher than this okay [Applause]
在这种情况下，显然是先生。恰佩尔（Chappel）好，让我们说一下
it's obviously in this case the for mr. Chappel good let's say this contest for
Chappel good let's say this contest for the student that gets different grades
获得不同年级的学生，其中一些也是通过保管来获得的，因此
the student that gets different grades and some is also from via safekeeping so
and some is also from via safekeeping so the let's accept this graph like that so
让我们接受这样的图表，这样我们就不必讨论所有细节了
the let's accept this graph like that so we don't have to discuss all the details
we don't have to discuss all the details but basically the parents of this are
但基本上，父母没有智力上的困难
but basically the parents of this are there's no difficulty in intelligence
there's no difficulty in intelligence but you know the socialist idea is a non
但是你知道社会主义的想法是一个非后裔权利，所以这不会
but you know the socialist idea is a non descender right so wouldn't be ni this
descender right so wouldn't be ni this no this is the friend of SAT okay the
不，这是SAT的朋友，好的，这是我正在讨论的内容
no this is the friend of SAT okay the note is something that I am discussing
note is something that I am discussing on the bottle but if you look at the
在瓶子上，但如果您在难度上看的方式大相径庭
on the bottle but if you look at the great differently in terms of difficulty
great differently in terms of difficulty alright it's not independent of the
好吧，这不是独立于字母的权利，因为这不是
alright it's not independent of the letter right because this is this is not
letter right because this is this is not in the list of the non-descendants okay
在非后裔列表中，所以给定a和G并不是独立的
in the list of the non-descendants okay so G is not independent well given a and
so G is not independent well given a and B
乙
关于推理的一点点，我们再次非常快地讨论，他们
so G is not independent well given a and B
a little bit about inference and again we discuss it very fast them and we were
关于推理的一点点，我们再次非常快地讨论，他们
we discuss it very fast them and we were spent at least two lectures to discuss
后来也花了至少两堂课讨论推理
spent at least two lectures to discuss inference later also right now
inference later also right now accept this as an introduction to the
将此作为本主题的介绍，而不是为了涵盖任何内容
accept this as an introduction to the topic not that we cover anything so for
topic not that we cover anything so for those who know about hidden Markov
那些了解隐马尔可夫模型的人，我想我们在第1课中看到了
those who know about hidden Markov models and I think we saw in lecture 1
models and I think we saw in lecture 1 we have a hidden state and we have some
我们有一个隐藏的状态，我们有一些嘈杂的条件，比如说观察结果
we have a hidden state and we have some noisy let's say observations maybe the
noisy let's say observations maybe the problem is to estimate the state given
问题是估计给定信息的状态，因为您知道我们什么时候
problem is to estimate the state given the information because you know when we
the information because you know when we say inference not only you try to say
说出推理，不仅是您尝试对已知的观察变量说些什么
say inference not only you try to say something about known observe variables
something about known observe variables but maybe there are lots of parameters
但是也许在模块中有很多参数启动了参数
but maybe there are lots of parameters started parameters in the module for
started parameters in the module for example we would say you know you
例如，我们会说您知道您分解了联合概率
example we would say you know you decompose the joint probability
decompose the joint probability distribution in conditionals
有条件的分布您是否注意到有条件的我们知道
distribution in conditionals did you notice conditional we know the
did you notice conditional we know the probability of x2 given x1 maybe have
给定x1的x2概率，您可能说对了一些参数定义
probability of x2 given x1 maybe have some parametric definition right you say
some parametric definition right you say this is defined by this table everything
这是由该表定义的一切都是孤独的，一切都是未知的
this is defined by this table everything is alone and everything is unknown means
is alone and everything is unknown means the toast probabilities in this table
该表中的烤面包概率是那些参数theta可以，所以
the toast probabilities in this table are those parameters theta all right so
are those parameters theta all right so there is how are you there are two
你好吗，有两件事对吧，一是估算
there is how are you there are two things right one is to estimate the
things right one is to estimate the scottie parameters theta and those
斯科蒂参数theta和那些优先级theta不会随着您的
scottie parameters theta and those priorities theta don't increase as your
priorities theta don't increase as your dataset increases so for example in the
数据集增加，例如在隐藏的马尔可夫模型中，您可以保持
dataset increases so for example in the hidden Markov model you can keep
hidden Markov model you can keep collecting data this theta will remain
收集数据，theta将保持不变
collecting data this theta will remain the same
the same ok and we will do those things later on
好的，我们稍后会做这些事情，但是阴影变量的数量
ok and we will do those things later on but the number of shaded variables
but the number of shaded variables increases the number of observation data
增加观察数据类型的数量增加还可以，所以从某种意义上讲
increases the number of observation data type increases okay so in some sense the
type increases okay so in some sense the hidden exists and treated differently
隐藏的存在与计算有所不同
hidden exists and treated differently from computing
from computing I'm gonna sleep in the morning okay so I
我要在早上睡觉好吧，所以我不知道我想告诉你
I'm gonna sleep in the morning okay so I I don't know I think I'm gonna show you
I don't know I think I'm gonna show you a slide or two an archery I'm surprised
一两张幻灯片，我很惊讶，但这没关系，我不知道为什么
a slide or two an archery I'm surprised but this is okay I don't know why this
but this is okay I don't know why this thinking here all right it doesn't
认为这里没关系，我认为实际上是在谈论
thinking here all right it doesn't matter I think actually talks about
matter I think actually talks about evidence we're gonna go to this light
证明我们要去了解这一点，所以这需要参数
evidence we're gonna go to this light bit so this takes the parameters people
bit so this takes the parameters people so let's say you know the conditional
假设您知道条件分布会改变您的图表
so let's say you know the conditional distributions change your graph so
distributions change your graph so that's why you stay conditioning or
这就是为什么您保持调理或theta的原因，所以我们不是油中毒的人
that's why you stay conditioning or theta so we're not people in the oil
theta so we're not people in the oil problems you do not know what we face
问题，您不知道我们要面对的事情，您必须完成但您知道theta
problems you do not know what we face you have to complete but you know theta
you have to complete but you know theta and you want given some evidence so
并且您想提供一些证据，因此这些是可见的注释，
and you want given some evidence so these are the visible notes the
these are the visible notes the invisible notes actually means like in
看不见的注释实际上意味着像此图中的预算注释还可以，
invisible notes actually means like in this graph the budget notes alright and
this graph the budget notes alright and then you want to say start thinking
那么您想说的是开始考虑山谷中的孩子们
then you want to say start thinking about the kids in the valleys to the
about the kids in the valleys to the hidden rocks so you want to compute the
隐藏的岩石，因此您想计算给定X 3且固定的XT的概率
hidden rocks so you want to compute the probability of XT given X 3 with fixed
probability of XT given X 3 with fixed parameters so effectively what you do is
如此有效的参数是一个简单的计算，我们这样说
parameters so effectively what you do is a simple calculation that we say this
a simple calculation that we say this the question there is a resonance a show
这个问题引起共鸣，表明你必须做所有的分母
the question there is a resonance a show that you have to do the denominator all
that you have to do the denominator all right this is a very important quantity
对，这是非常重要的数量，这基本上是证据
right this is a very important quantity this is the evidence this is basically
this is the evidence this is basically tells you how probable are the data that
告诉您观察到的数据有多可能
tells you how probable are the data that you have observed
you have observed okay so this is how you calculate the
好的，这就是您计算证据的方式，并且需要分子
okay so this is how you calculate the evidence and in the numerator you need
evidence and in the numerator you need the Joint Commission of the kid another
这个孩子的联合委员会的另一个车身，但我可以告诉你的方式
the Joint Commission of the kid another vehicle body but the way I can tell you
vehicle body but the way I can tell you and it may be on a coming slide that if
如果您想在其中发布步骤或问题，可能会在即将到来的幻灯片上
and it may be on a coming slide that if you want to post a step or a problem in
you want to post a step or a problem in this area how do we compute this
这个区域我们如何有效地计算参数theta
this area how do we compute this parameters theta effectively
parameters theta effectively you compute the parameters by maximizing
您通过最大化作为分母T的证据来计算参数
you compute the parameters by maximizing the evidence which is the denominator T
the evidence which is the denominator T of XT given theta all right so
XT的给定theta很好，所以
好吧，我们不需要这个生活，我们需要一些局部细节，所以这
the evidence which is the denominator T of XT given theta all right so
okay we don't need this life we'll need some partial details so this
好吧，我们不需要这个生活，我们需要一些局部细节，所以这
we'll need some partial details so this is actually I mentioned that see that
实际上，我提到看到您要对其进行计算，以最大程度地提高
is actually I mentioned that see that you want to compute it you maximize the
you want to compute it you maximize the evidence don't pay attention to this one
证据不关注这里的这一点到第二点我在这里做了什么
evidence don't pay attention to this one here to the second what have I done here
here to the second what have I done here before I had the probability of X being
在我将X赋予theta的概率之前，在这里我写了这是
before I had the probability of X being given theta so here I wrote this this is
given theta so here I wrote this this is sort of my new evidence the
我的新证据是对数似然数据逻辑，但我有
sort of my new evidence the log-likelihood data logical but I have
log-likelihood data logical but I have done something else the fact I wrote the
我做了另一件事，事实是我在N上写了目的地，这是什么
done something else the fact I wrote the destination over N so what is this
destination over N so what is this summation you think why is Tommy what is
总结你认为汤米为什么是N什么是大写N
summation you think why is Tommy what is N what's capital N
隐藏的字母看不到湖人在这里说只有一个
the hidden letters not see the Lakers here say there's only one who do
here say there's only one who do calculate the likelihood right you
计算您使数据寿命最大化的可能性
calculate the likelihood right you maximize the life of the data what is
maximize the life of the data what is the assumption implicitly implied by
这样写就暗含的假设是我的广告数据
the assumption implicitly implied by writing like this that my data by ad
writing like this that my data by ad okay all right so so basically we're
好吧，所以基本上，我们正在尝试过滤掉减去日志的数据
okay all right so so basically we're trying to filter that much minus the log
trying to filter that much minus the log likelihood and also just analyze the
并仅分析最重要的问题
likelihood and also just analyze the problem which is the preeminent to
problem which is the preeminent to computing a map estimate I have added
计算地图估算值我在这里添加了对theta堆的爱
computing a map estimate I have added here the love of the pile of theta right
here the love of the pile of theta right so this likely Qin times the prior they
所以这可能是Qin乘以theta的后验值，好吧，再见
so this likely Qin times the prior they give you the posterior of theta okay see
give you the posterior of theta okay see the values are not there can be anything
价值观是不存在的，任何事情都可以，所以要认真解决这个问题，并且
the values are not there can be anything any ground okay so much smizing this and
any ground okay so much smizing this and performing this problem you get you
执行此问题，您将获得点参数，再次，我们将看到
performing this problem you get you point parameters and again we will see
point parameters and again we will see this problem in detail with a lot of
稍后会提供大量数值和分析结果，详细说明此问题
this problem in detail with a lot of numerical and analytical results later
numerical and analytical results later on in the course cause it's a good idea
因为这是一个好主意，所以知道它的含义是个好主意
on in the course cause it's a good idea to know what it means
to know what it means completing the hidden variables
完成隐藏变量的参数sleep
completing the hidden variables parameters sleep
对，还有另一个问题，也许我们将在四月份非常接近
right and another problem that maybe we will discuss in April very close to the
will discuss in April very close to the end of the semester would be this
学期末是这个问题，它会在链接下出现
end of the semester would be this problem it goes under the links not
problem it goes under the links not celerity so for example in our sprinkle
速度，例如，在我们的玻璃杯洒水问题中，我们说
celerity so for example in our sprinkle with glass problem let's say got a
with glass problem let's say got a different day somebody does observations
如果洒水喷头开着，在多云的日子有人进行观察
different day somebody does observations when it's cloudy if the sprinkler is on
when it's cloudy if the sprinkler is on it drains with the grass is wet and you
它的排水口被草弄湿了​​，您收集了我做过的数据，所以
it drains with the grass is wet and you collect amounts of data on I did data so
collect amounts of data on I did data so maybe somebody will ask if I have this
也许有人会问我是否有这个观察结果，你能为我解决吗
maybe somebody will ask if I have this observation can you figure it out for me
observation can you figure it out for me what is the graph that represents these
什么是代表这些观察结果的图，您知道的唯一方法是
what is the graph that represents these observations the only ways you know can
observations the only ways you know can you tell me that particular differential
你告诉我，特别的差别是没有防雨的阴霾很多
you tell me that particular differential being cloudy of not rain defense a lot
being cloudy of not rain defense a lot with grass defense of sprinkler rain etc
带有洒水小雨等的草防御
这个问题实际上是错误的，因为它是一种结构学习问题，请参见
being cloudy of not rain defense a lot with grass defense of sprinkler rain etc
this problem effectively is false as a structure learning problem and see this
这个问题实际上是错误的，因为它是一种结构学习问题，请参见
structure learning problem and see this as follows G you can get the log
如下所示，您可以正确获取数据的对数似然，因此
as follows G you can get the log likelihood of the data all right so the
likelihood of the data all right so the problem here is find the graph G that
这里的问题是找到使当天的对数可能性最大化的图G
problem here is find the graph G that maximizes the log likelihood of the day
maximizes the log likelihood of the day all right so for each graph like this
好的，所以对于每个像这样的图，例如，您都可以
all right so for each graph like this graph for example you can go and
graph for example you can go and calculate this okay
计算这个好吧，如果您计算那么很多
calculate this okay and if you calculate then for many
and if you calculate then for many graphs you can say finding the graph
您可以说找到图来最大化该图，这有点
graphs you can say finding the graph that maximizes that and this is sort of
that maximizes that and this is sort of a penalty terms to be sure that you
惩罚性条款，以确保您没有过于复杂的图表，我们
a penalty terms to be sure that you don't have an overly complex graph we
don't have an overly complex graph we discussed a bit about these things in
在秋天的平衡中讨论了一些关于这些事情的内容
discussed a bit about these things in the fall of the balance of
the fall of the balance of between keeping the data and complexity
在保持数据正确性和复杂性之间保持平衡，因此您不想过度使用它
between keeping the data and complexity right so you don't want to overdo it
right so you don't want to overdo it again we will come up to this problem in
再次，我们会遇到这个问题，有时我们需要一棵树好了，我想
again we will come up to this problem in sometimes we need a tree okay and I want
sometimes we need a tree okay and I want to introduce one more from the mental
从您可能具有传统的心理概念中再引入一个
to introduce one more from the mental concept that you may have traditional
concept that you may have traditional programming and hopefully Tuvok takes
编程，并希望Tuvok记下与此有关的注释
programming and hopefully Tuvok takes notes on this that has to do with
notes on this that has to do with ancestral subject okay because this is
祖先的主题好吧，因为这对您来说非常重要
ancestral subject okay because this is sort of a very essential for you know
sort of a very essential for you know clever and distribution of it a graph
聪明和它的分布图，你想采取充分的样本
clever and distribution of it a graph and you want to take samples full of
and you want to take samples full of distribution there is a very efficient
分发有一种非常有效的方法来执行此操作，因此请记住
distribution there is a very efficient way of doing this so remember in in in
way of doing this so remember in in in directed graphs right the distribution
有向图的分布是正确的，可以说我们有一个链条，所以
directed graphs right the distribution was let's say we have a chain okay so
was let's say we have a chain okay so the probability of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 3 is
X 1 X 2 X 3 X 3的概率是X 1乘以
the probability of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 3 is the probability of X 1 times the
the probability of X 1 times the probability of x2 given X 2 and 5 the
给定X 2时x2的概率为5，给定X 2或in时x 3的概率
probability of x2 given X 2 and 5 the probability of X 3 given X 2 or in
probability of X 3 given X 2 or in general we have a product of the
总的来说，我们有一个概率效应的乘积，甚至是父母
general we have a product of the probability effect and even the parents
probability effect and even the parents of all right so I'm just on something
好吧，所以我只是在一些样品上，我们对此条样品进行了采样
of all right so I'm just on something the sample we take a sample of this bar
the sample we take a sample of this bar and with such 1/2 let's say X K or
用1/2来说XK或极限，我们开始说话了
and with such 1/2 let's say X K or extreme we do is you start talking
extreme we do is you start talking interest from the probability P x1 we
从概率P x1的兴趣开始，我们从根音开始，然后是样本
interest from the probability P x1 we start with the root note then the sample
start with the root note then the sample the problem there if you sample from the
如果您仍然从条件效果中取样，就会出现问题
the problem there if you sample from the conditional effect still given the
conditional effect still given the participant still and the part of it
仍然是参与者，它的一部分基本上仍然是x1
participant still and the part of it still basically is x1 which already
still basically is x1 which already focused on hope right and then the
专注于希望权，然后在给定X的幂的情况下将X 3的概率
focused on hope right and then the probability of X 3 given the powers of X
probability of X 3 given the powers of X 3 which I will assume are x1 and x2
我假设3是x1和x2对，所以您基本上是从
3 which I will assume are x1 and x2 right so you basically proceed from the
right so you basically proceed from the root to the left
从左边开始向左反击
root to the left countering first from this marginal and
countering first from this marginal and then from this conditional and this is
然后从这个条件开始，这被称为祖先
then from this conditional and this is called ancestral soundly
called ancestral soundly and there's many algorithm this thing in
蒙特卡洛（Montecarlo）参考文献中有很多算法
and there's many algorithm this thing in Montecarlo reference that sort of take
Montecarlo reference that sort of take advantage of that so in other ways if
这样做的好处是，如果分布在50维附近
advantage of that so in other ways if the distribution is 50 dimensional near
the distribution is 50 dimensional near South Point between dimensions the
维度之间的南点（极低维度的样本）
South Point between dimensions the sample from very low dimensional
sample from very low dimensional distributions by taking a particular in
通过采取特殊的效果，我们意识到
distributions by taking a particular in effect they we realizations of the
effect they we realizations of the directions on the box makes a bit of
盒子上的指示有点合理，选举中有很多事情
directions on the box makes a bit of sense okay so many things from election
sense okay so many things from election to with another little concept and those
还有一个小概念，那些在马尔可夫毯子里的好毯子是
to with another little concept and those within a Markov blanket okay blanket is
within a Markov blanket okay blanket is the set of nodes that render Sanofi
有条件地使Sanofi脱离所有文件夹的节点集
the set of nodes that render Sanofi conditionally independent of folder all
conditionally independent of folder all the nodes in the dock in other ways what
以其他方式在坞站中的节点是多少？
the nodes in the dock in other ways what is the minimal number of nodes which I
is the minimal number of nodes which I need to know so that no information from
需要知道，以便没有来自其他节点的信息，我们会有所作为
need to know so that no information from any other nodes we make any difference
any other nodes we make any difference in my about saying something about the T
在我讲关于T no no T的一些事情时，它是节点集，但是
in my about saying something about the T no no T so it's the set of nodes but
no no T so it's the set of nodes but make the node conditional independence
使节点有条件独立，图中的所有其他节点都可以
make the node conditional independence all the other nodes in a graph okay
all the other nodes in a graph okay and so let me just tell you that what it
所以我只告诉你它的组成
and so let me just tell you that what it consists of
it consists of the violence of the node the hindrance of the node and the
它由节点的暴力，节点的障碍和
the hindrance of the node and the copilot of the node right because some
节点副驾驶正确，因为某些节点步距太远，因此组件
copilot of the node right because some node step too far and so the components
node step too far and so the components of the road so can you tell me what is
的道路，所以你能告诉我毯子的印记是什么
of the road so can you tell me what is the mark of blanket
the mark of blanket no talk huh I'm here 23 no there are 23
没话说吧，我在这里23不，父亲下面有23个，所以你让我流浪
no talk huh I'm here 23 no there are 23 under father so you let me wander
under father so you let me wander without the children five six and seven
没有孩子的五，六，七岁，是什么组成部分？
without the children five six and seven and what are the components what are the
and what are the components what are the components of five you notice Frank is a
五分之一的成分，您会注意到弗兰克是七岁的孩子，如果您不能
components of five you notice Frank is a a kid seven and if you can't another
a kid seven and if you can't another father or mother for of poor is a
穷人的父亲或母亲是长久的好父母
father or mother for of poor is a co-parent of long time okay
co-parent of long time okay now you may ask me
现在你可能会问我，你知道这有什么证据吗
now you may ask me you know is there any proof of this
you know is there any proof of this place is coming and I'm going to at
这个地方来了，我至少要在一张幻灯片中强调它的存在
place is coming and I'm going to at least highlight its being in one slide
least highlight its being in one slide to see this but then the Marfa Blanca
看到这个，然后是Marfa Blanca森林二和三的五个
to see this but then the Marfa Blanca the five of the forest two and three
the five of the forest two and three right the children six and seven and
对六个孩子和七个孩子，然后在这种情况下，很酷的父母是
right the children six and seven and then the cool parents in this case is
then the cool parents in this case is for so basically knowing two three four
因为基本上知道二三四六和七
for so basically knowing two three four six and seven
six and seven no fives in the friend of node 1 okay so
在节点1的朋友中没有击掌，所以从本质上讲，请与本笔记隔离
no fives in the friend of node 1 okay so in essence think with this notes isolate
in essence think with this notes isolate note 5 all right
注意5可以将其余5个分开
note 5 all right the separation of five from the rest of
the separation of five from the rest of the launch integral ok and and actually
发射积分确定，实际上这件事做了这张图所示的事情
the launch integral ok and and actually this thing did what this graph shows
this thing did what this graph shows let's say this is this other parent
假设这是另一位父母，好吧，这些是孩子
let's say this is this other parent all right these are the children which
all right these are the children which are the copilot from knowing all this
是副驾驶，不知道所有这些信息，这是什么
are the copilot from knowing all this information separate this is what's a
information separate this is what's a blanket which sort of to isolate X from
覆盖将X与图的其余部分隔离开来的那种
blanket which sort of to isolate X from the rest of the graph an extremely sort
the rest of the graph an extremely sort of important idea here all right the
重要想法的想法可以使绘画父母和所有人
of important idea here all right the drawing parents and again everybody
drawing parents and again everybody forgets not the components come in the
忘记没有组件出现在图片中，就像您知道第四个
forgets not the components come in the picture okay like you know the fourth
picture okay like you know the fourth year list extremely important so we do
年份清单非常重要，因此我们以这个例子为例
year list extremely important so we do this example
this example so any highlight the point okay it's you
因此，任何强调这一点的人都可以，这是您所知道的很多事情
so any highlight the point okay it's you know a lot of these things terms of
know a lot of these things terms of their authors but I want you to sort of
他们的作者，但我希望您能体会到他们不是来自北方
their authors but I want you to sort of realize that they don't come from north
realize that they don't come from north where there is some common sense
那里有一些常识推导，所以说
where there is some common sense derivation there so let's say
我们知道我们可能不会全神贯注所有相关笔记，但没有死的可能性是什么
we know the probability we won't me all the relevant notes but no die what's the
the relevant notes but no die what's the problem being to fix all right remember
问题是要解决所有问题，记得我们说市场是
problem being to fix all right remember we said the market market is the
we said the market market is the strength of the notes the thighs the
大腿的音符强度，从其他部位知道眼睛
strength of the notes the thighs the lays know the eye from the rest of the
lays know the eye from the rest of the notes so you need to know from what is
音符，所以您需要知道这是什么表现无限取决于进位
notes so you need to know from what is this perform infinity depends on carry
this perform infinity depends on carry put it basically excited given all the
鉴于所有其他注释，基本上让我感到兴奋，我要问的是
put it basically excited given all the other notes and what I'm asking is do I
other notes and what I'm asking is do I really need all the other notes or some
真的需要所有其他笔记或我们中的一些人，您知道这基本上是我们来的
really need all the other notes or some of us you know it's basically we come to
of us you know it's basically we come to they are important so when I could not
它们很重要，所以当我做不到的时候，我将其写为联合概率
they are important so when I could not is I wrote this as the joint probability
is I wrote this as the joint probability of for the notes in the mouth in the
田径比赛中嘴里的音符，他一直在-我有
of for the notes in the mouth in the track event and here he kept - I have
track event and here he kept - I have the probability of list of quarter notes
四分音符列表Mathathari的概率，所以我必须具体化
the probability of list of quarter notes Mathari so I have to materialize my out
Mathari so I have to materialize my out so I use the factorization on the top is
所以我在顶部使用分解是在底部的授权
so I use the factorization on the top is an authorization on the bottom okay
an authorization on the bottom okay and now though I don't want you to need
现在，尽管我不希望您在这里需要任何东西，所以不要
and now though I don't want you to need anything here right so don't get
anything here right so don't get polluted by reading look this ratio and
阅读此书会污染该比率，并弄清楚您有时知道哪些术语
polluted by reading look this ratio and figure out what terms you know sometimes
figure out what terms you know sometimes are going to cancel from the numerator
将要取消分子和分母剩下的
are going to cancel from the numerator and denominator what is going to be left
and denominator what is going to be left there so here I have the whole
在那里，这里我有整个分布，他们就像有X
there so here I have the whole distribution and they're like have X
distribution and they're like have X trying to graveyard so what is left what
试图墓地，所以剩下的是什么，什么是通用术语
trying to graveyard so what is left what is what are the common terms doesn't
is what are the common terms doesn't disappear so that this X I who made a
消失了，使这个与时间有关的十一世
disappear so that this X I who made a time dependent
time dependent given this Markov Blanca dimension so
考虑到马尔可夫·布兰卡（Markov Blanca）的这个尺寸，所以您所知道的称为消失
given this Markov Blanca dimension so what you know term some disappearing
what you know term some disappearing from this ratio
从这个比例
寻找您更清楚的是他们会留哪些音符
what you know term some disappearing from this ratio
look for you know even better what notes are they going to stay in that
寻找您更清楚的是他们会留哪些音符
are they going to stay in that calculation
计算
我的想法不是很好
are they going to stay in that calculation
with my mind that's not very good
好吧，它的右上角有一个集成件，所以让我们看一下
okay so there is an integration care of its high right so let's see in in this
its high right so let's see in in this product there is a distribution of X my
产品有X的分布我给父母的权利女士
product there is a distribution of X my given the parent right ladies
given the parent right ladies distributions that involves the children
考虑到正确的政治因素，涉及儿童的分布
distributions that involves the children given the politics i right
given the politics i right and those distributions involve also the
这些分布还涉及副驾驶，您会看到我的意思是在这里
and those distributions involve also the copilot you see that I mean somehow here
copilot you see that I mean somehow here because an integrative annex I write in
因为有一个综合性附件，我在分母中写了任何与之相关的内容
because an integrative annex I write in the denominator anything that relates
the denominator anything that relates book starring of the top has to stay
最高层主演的书必须留在那儿，这种关系所包含的内容
book starring of the top has to stay there and what this relations contain at
there and what this relations contain at tie is the distribution of X i given its
领带是X i赋予父母的权利的分布
tie is the distribution of X i given its parents right
parents right nice ghostie nodes and then the
好的幽灵节点，然后XI中的子节点的分布
nice ghostie nodes and then the distribution of the children of X I in
distribution of the children of X I in that differential from the co-pilot
与副驾驶员的差异，所以这个孩子依靠手推车
that differential from the co-pilot so this children depends on the trolley
so this children depends on the trolley and the copilot you see those are the
而且您看到的副驾驶是所有显示器的唯一分布，所以
and the copilot you see those are the only distributions of any display yep so
only distributions of any display yep so basically this type of nodes that you
基本上，您看到的这种类型的节点具有Naga的标记
basically this type of nodes that you see there are the mark of Naga
现在市场所想要的基本上提供了一种非常有效的计算方式
now the so the market wanted basically gives a very efficient way for computing
gives a very efficient way for computing the probability of a now given all the
现在赋予所有其他节点正确的概率，因为我们说
the probability of a now given all the other nodes all right because we said
other nodes all right because we said this probably the only depends on the
这可能是唯一取决于父母的父母和孩子好吗
this probably the only depends on the parents for parents and children okay
parents for parents and children okay and I did it here one example of the
我在这里做了一个例子，给出了其他所有情况下X 5的概率
and I did it here one example of the probability of X 5 given all the other
probability of X 5 given all the other I'm sorry given all the nodes with type
对于所有类型为right的节点，我很抱歉，您可以将其写为
I'm sorry given all the nodes with type right you can write this reverse the
right you can write this reverse the factorization of the Joint Distribution
联合分配的因式分解，唯一的付款条件在给定的情况下过期
factorization of the Joint Distribution the only terms of pay is expired given
the only terms of pay is expired given experience three right five depends on
经历三对五取决于父母，孩子取决于五
experience three right five depends on the parents children depending on five
the parents children depending on five and three right and then notice what
和三个权利，然后注意我们从来没有几个依赖于
and three right and then notice what else we never have several depending on
else we never have several depending on five and six the parlance and the
五和六的用语和副驾驶为一个案例，为什么我在这里指出
five and six the parlance and the copilot for a case why I indicated here
copilot for a case why I indicated here for five states in this calculation can
对于这个计算中的五个州，这里可以很好地写在这里
for five states in this calculation can here well it's written here again those
here well it's written here again those who have taken courses for should the
谁参加了该课程的计算统计课程，其中
who have taken courses for should the computational statistics course in which
computational statistics course in which means in the fall we recognize basically
意味着在秋天，我们基本上认识到业务需要做的分配
means in the fall we recognize basically business the distribution we need to do
business the distribution we need to do get something right so this is the
得到正确的东西，所以这是我们需要给予的认知
get something right so this is the cognition we need to give to give
cognition we need to give to give something and you see a nice
某些东西，您会看到很好的受精方式，请记住排序
something and you see a nice fertilization to keep in mind the sort
fertilization to keep in mind the sort of idea so far instead of something and
到目前为止的想法，而不是某些东西，马尔可夫毯子的概念欢迎您
of idea so far instead of something and the concept of Markov blanket welcome to
the concept of Markov blanket welcome to camp with a very nice implementation of
通过很好的入门实现来扎营
camp with a very nice implementation of get started
get started so we will assure give you homework from
所以我们保证很快就会给你作业
so we will assure give you homework from this soon okay
this soon okay so let me summarize and then we're done
所以让我总结一下，然后在给您的情况下完成对所有知识的演讲
so let me summarize and then we're done with lecture to every know given the you
with lecture to every know given the you know descendants okay now try moving the
知道后代好吧，现在尝试移动父级独立于
know descendants okay now try moving the parent is independent of the
parent is independent of the non-disabled and I assume for the
非残障人士，我认为对于父母和前辈来说，
non-disabled and I assume for the parents and the predecessors are a
parents and the predecessors are a subset of the you know descendants so T
您知道后代的子集，因此T独立于三个被告
subset of the you know descendants so T is independent of the three defendants
is independent of the three defendants given the powers and so this is called
给定的权力，所以这被称为指令局部马尔可夫属性
given the powers and so this is called the directive local Markov property this
the directive local Markov property this is called the order Markov property we
被称为订单马尔可夫财产，我们可以欣赏为什么它是伦敦的
is called the order Markov property we can appreciate why it's for London
can appreciate why it's for London because in essence this knowledge of
因为从本质上讲，这种在T数之前的编号知识
because in essence this knowledge of numbering that is before the number of T
因此，此本地属性L会立即向您提供马尔可夫属性的订单
so this local property L immediately gives to you the order Markov property
gives to you the order Markov property because this is a subset of the known
因为这是已知家属的子集，所以有趣的是
because this is a subset of the known dependents what is interesting is if
dependents what is interesting is if this property is true then also the
这个属性是正确的，那么其他属性也是正确的，
this property is true then also the other properties to all right and that
other properties to all right and that makes a bit of calculation if you are
进行一些计算，如果您有兴趣，可以阅读此举
makes a bit of calculation if you are interested you can read this move for
interested you can read this move for the derivation so effectively this still
如此有效地推导，仍然具有马尔可夫性质，并且
the derivation so effectively this still Markov properties are equivalent and
Markov properties are equivalent and both of them can be shown that they are
他们两个都可以证明它们等效于我们的极化
both of them can be shown that they are equivalent with a polarization that we
equivalent with a polarization that we have seen you know talking in lecture
看到你知道在第一堂课中讲话
have seen you know talking in lecture one
one electric drums so again a local property
电鼓又是一个地方财产，一个订购马尔可夫财产，这个
electric drums so again a local property an order Markov property and this
an order Markov property and this factorization you can feel from one of
您可以从其中之一感受到因式分解，可以证明其他因素
factorization you can feel from one of them you can prove what the other ones
them you can prove what the other ones and the other way around
反过来说，在一些小例子中还记得
and the other way around remember in some of the little examples
remember in some of the little examples we did without the information we were
我们在没有信息的情况下做到了，我们证明您知道某种身份，但是
we did without the information we were proving you know sort of identities but
proving you know sort of identities but also you can prove that starting with
你也可以证明从任何一个开始就可以解决一个地区
also you can prove that starting with any of this you can solve a district
any of this you can solve a district relationship one can
关系可以
我必须在午餐时间喝点咖啡，因为从我的系统开始
any of this you can solve a district relationship one can
I have to drink some coffee at lunchtime because from my system it's gotten at
我必须在午餐时间喝点咖啡，因为从我的系统开始
because from my system it's gotten at this time and without it we may still
这次，没有它，我们可能仍然会在这个小地方一样，但是一个
this time and without it we may still equally in this little here okay but one
equally in this little here okay but one day I'm sure that you see all the coffee
那天，我敢肯定，您会发现我头顶上所有的咖啡都没有付
day I'm sure that you see all the coffee coming on the top of me not paying
coming on the top of me not paying attention because talking and drinking
注意，因为可以继续聊天和喝咖啡而不是丛林
attention because talking and drinking coffees not the jungle can be continued
coffees not the jungle can be continued so drinking wine isn't talking
所以喝酒不是很好，这会有点
so drinking wine isn't talking alright and this is going to be a little
alright and this is going to be a little bit weird it's not very public is
有点奇怪，它不是很公开，基本上是图形化的图形显示方式
bit weird it's not very public is basically the graphical way to figure
basically the graphical way to figure out what independence relations you have
找出你在图中有什么独立关系好吧，所以我们想
out what independence relations you have in a graph okay so we want to dis have a
in a graph okay so we want to dis have a calculation so I'll go under the name
计算，所以我将以这种分离为名
calculation so I'll go under the name this separation is what is going to
this separation is what is going to allow us to figure out independence in
让我们找出图表中的独立性，所以我不得不承认
allow us to figure out independence in the graph so I have to admit when you
the graph so I have to admit when you first see them this may sound a little
首先看到他们，这听起来可能有点怪异，我要做的唯一一件事是
first see them this may sound a little bit weird the only thing I'm going to
bit weird the only thing I'm going to say just our homes because Rose has to
说我们的家，因为玫瑰必须决定，您可以世俗地满足
say just our homes because Rose has to decide and you can secular satisfied
decide and you can secular satisfied then you can test independence
然后你可以测试独立性关系
then you can test independence relationships
relationships so this'll look like something will
所以这看起来像是某种驱动力，因此我们不能因为这个原因你可以
so this'll look like something will drive we cannot for this reason you can
drive we cannot for this reason you can solve that they're equivalent to this
解决它们等同于我们在本地标记的属性
solve that they're equivalent to this local mark of properties that we
local mark of properties that we discussed before and this will go on the
之前讨论过，这将继续使用分离的名称，因此那里的定义
discussed before and this will go on the name the separation so definitions there
name the separation so definitions there is way too much information that's right
太多的信息是正确的，所以让我们逐行且无方向地走
is way too much information that's right so let's go line by line and undirected
so let's go line by line and undirected path is this separated by a set of nodes
路径是由一组节点II隔开的，因此他清楚地暗示了以下注释：
path is this separated by a set of nodes II so he clearly implies the notes that
II so he clearly implies the notes that I know about the evidence so an
我知道证据，因此如果位于
I know about the evidence so an undirected graph is the separated if at
undirected graph is the separated if at least one of the Tony Hawk so in the
至少是托尼·霍克（Tony Hawk）之一，所以在各种图表中您都可以看到这是我的
least one of the Tony Hawk so in the various graphs that you see this is my
various graphs that you see this is my evidence right this is my evidence
正确的证据，这是我的证据，所以这里从X到Z的路径正确
evidence right this is my evidence so here the path from X to Z right the
so here the path from X to Z right the arrows point in this way but
箭头以这种方式指向，但也可以找到相反的方式，因此它可以
arrows point in this way but can also find the opposite way so it can
can also find the opposite way so it can be this or that so in this case we say
是这个或那个，在这种情况下，我们说x和z与Y分开，如果
be this or that so in this case we say that x and z are be separated from Y if
that x and z are be separated from Y if Y is observed okay so a lot of times
观察到Y很好，所以很多时候你所说的基本上是
Y is observed okay so a lot of times what you say basically is whenever this
what you say basically is whenever this node and you see the arrow converging
节点，您会看到箭头融合了这个机会和尾巴，所以如果您有
node and you see the arrow converging this chance and tail so if you have
this chance and tail so if you have heads entailed already obtained and
头需要已经获得，并分享相反的方式，这是
heads entailed already obtained and shares the other way around and this is
shares the other way around and this is an observed node the next year this
第二年给该操作员一个观察节点，好吧。帕雷蒂
an observed node the next year this operator is given Y okay mr. Paretti so
operator is given Y okay mr. Paretti so you can you can start getting the
您可以开始正确理解这个概念，这意味着他们是德克萨斯人
you can you can start getting the concept right means the Texans they're
concept right means the Texans they're independent really given Y reinstitute
独立的真正给定的Y重新通过X而不是X真正丰富了Z
independent really given Y reinstitute not really rich Z from X by going
not really rich Z from X by going through the evidence known why okay and
通过已知的证据证明为什么还可以，以及您看到的这种小块
through the evidence known why okay and this sort of little blocks that you see
this sort of little blocks that you see on the bottom that's what they indicate
它们指示的是底部，但从某种意义上说，从X到Z的路径是
on the bottom that's what they indicate but somehow the path from X to Z is
but somehow the path from X to Z is broke if you observe why okay I'm
如果您观察为什么会坏，那么我在那里扔了很多术语，但是
broke if you observe why okay I'm throwing a lots of terminology there but
throwing a lots of terminology there but so this is one part of the definition if
因此，如果您遇到这种情况并明智地观察，那么这就是定义的一部分
so this is one part of the definition if you have this situation and wise observe
you have this situation and wise observe okay excellent zero disparate from Y
好，与Y的差值为零，另一种情况是，如果您有股票
okay excellent zero disparate from Y another case is when if you have a stock
another case is when if you have a stock situation right so this is the parent
情况正确，所以这是父母指向两个孩子，所以我们再次
situation right so this is the parent pointing into two children so again we
pointing into two children so again we contain support and wise and evidence
然后包含支持，智慧和证据，并被Y隔开
contain support and wise and evidence excellency then and be separated by Y so
excellency then and be separated by Y so again you notice the path is indicated
再次，您注意到此处指示了路径，因为Z阻止了Z
again you notice the path is indicated here products the Z is blocked because Y
here products the Z is blocked because Y doesn't allow this to go through
不允许这样做，并尝试从X到Z或从种子
doesn't allow this to go through and try to go from X to Z or from seed
and try to go from X to Z or from seed to X the pocketbook have instead what's
到口袋里的X却与独立性有什么关系
to X the pocketbook have instead what's the relation with independence for
the relation with independence for anything I'm defining I'm just giving
我正在定义的任何内容我只是在给出一些定义，但是我们可以
anything I'm defining I'm just giving some definitions right but we can
some definitions right but we can motivate what these definitions are
激发这些定义的正确性，所以我们将再次
motivate what these definitions are going to be about okay so again we will
going to be about okay so again we will show that in this case given Y and
显示在这种情况下，给定Y并与给定的Y共享此fork结构
show that in this case given Y and sharing this fork structure with Y given
sharing this fork structure with Y given being in the evidence actions here
在给定Y和条件的情况下在证据行动中有条件地独立
being in the evidence actions here conditionally independent given Y and
conditionally independent given Y and then of course we have this explaining
那么我们当然可以用这种解释方式来解释X和G为
then of course we have this explaining away situation where we have X and G be
away situation where we have X and G be the causes of the same Y right so the
导致相同的Y的原因正确，因此，此处的箭头是重组
the causes of the same Y right so the arrows bullet at this is a restructure
arrows bullet at this is a restructure and notice that the patient suddenly
并注意到病人突然改变了
and notice that the patient suddenly changed
changed it says they contain service trucks like
它说他们包含像这样的服务卡车，我们说Z中的文字是
it says they contain service trucks like that and we say the text in Z are
that and we say the text in Z are dissipated if the destruction like math
如果像数学和y这样的破坏没有在证据中消失，为什么不消失
dissipated if the destruction like math and y is not in the evidence why is not
and y is not in the evidence why is not observed so in other ways the path from
观察到，因此，如果y不安全，则从X到Z的路径将被阻塞
observed so in other ways the path from X to Z is block if y is not a safe
完美，为什么没有设置好
perfect why is nothing set okay
所以基本上，如果没有明智地观察，我们会在漫画界看到
so basically if wise not observed we will see in the comics life that
will see in the comics life that excellency you know are they will give
您知道的是，他们会给这个例子，我们对X和Z说了什么
excellency you know are they will give this example what did we say for X and Z
this example what did we say for X and Z alone what did we say there were
独自一人，我们说了什么，那帅哥没有防备，所以
alone what did we say there were handsome undefended all right so
handsome undefended all right so obviously this wise and himself I know
显然，这个智者和他本人我不知道大炮的优越性
obviously this wise and himself I know not the excellency of artillery
not the excellency of artillery independent once I observed why they
我观察到他们为什么变得依赖后就独立了
independent once I observed why they become dependent okay
因此，在我们完成操作之前，您已经知道XY和z注释，但是您可以告诉您，
so before we had done you you know XY &amp; z notes but you can tell relies this to
z notes but you can tell relies this to a set of notes or fear percentage we
一组注释或恐惧百分比，我们不说在给定图中说
a set of notes or fear percentage we don't say we say that in a given graph
don't say we say that in a given graph is dissipated from a set of notes be
从一组音符中耗散，在没有第60步的情况下得到一些证据
is dissipated from a set of notes be given some evidence on the step of no 60
given some evidence on the step of no 60 if basically this is be separated from
如果基本上将其与给定的e分开，则尝试神秘
if basically this is be separated from the given e so to try to mystical for
the given e so to try to mystical for any note way to an old in me to be
以任何方式向我中的老人证明是知道这部分是可以的
any note way to an old in me to be evidence knows that part is block okay
evidence knows that part is block okay using the rules that we have seen so so
使用我们已经看到的规则，所以这可能涉及一个小角度
using the rules that we have seen so so this may involve a small angle it right
this may involve a small angle it right I mean the thing is you know when you
我的意思是，当您开始正确地放置此主题时，您就知道了
I mean the thing is you know when you start putting this topics in place right
start putting this topics in place right 350 years ago when people doing that you
350年前，当人们这样做时，您可以称呼任何您知道的东西
350 years ago when people doing that you can call anything anything you know so
can call anything anything you know so the idea is I don't know the history I
我的想法是我不知道先生的历史。多变
the idea is I don't know the history I think is very possible mr. Vaile
think is very possible mr. Vaile reference 98 introduced responsible very
参考98引入的负责人很小，所以这个想法是要以图形方式
reference 98 introduced responsible very small so the idea is to to graphically
small so the idea is to to graphically business operation the probable and you
可能会进行业务操作，并且您尝试将文本扔掉而使球变形
business operation the probable and you try to shape a ball that you throw text
try to shape a ball that you throw text can reach Z all right and you have some
可以很好地达到Z，并且您有一些规则，最好的日期告诉您何时
can reach Z all right and you have some rules the best date tells you when the
rules the best date tells you when the ball can pass through and evidence we
球可以通过，我们都不知道的证据
ball can pass through and evidence we all don't know
all don't know okay and so if you can read Z then
好的，所以如果您可以阅读Z，那么基本上，如果您
okay and so if you can read Z then basically the path is not block if you
basically the path is not block if you cannot reach the path is blocked and the
无法到达路径被阻塞，并且在有证据的情况下注释是独立的
cannot reach the path is blocked and the notes are independent given the evidence
notes are independent given the evidence so basically this is the same picture
所以基本上，这是我们以前所见的同一幅画，但再想一想
so basically this is the same picture that we had before but again think
that we had before but again think you're throwing it home and it's
你把它扔回家，在东北很重要的一首歌叫做
you're throwing it home and it's important on the northeast a song called
important on the northeast a song called the most in travel offers it to be as
旅行中最多的东西是正确的方向
the most in travel offers it to be as directions right
directions right and this has to do with the fact that
这与事实有关，在这种情况下，您知道箭头
and this has to do with the fact that you know like in this case the arrows
you know like in this case the arrows can look the other direction as well you
可以看到另一个方向，您得到相同的结果，所以大多数人可以拥有
can look the other direction as well you get the same result so the most can have
get the same result so the most can have an opposite to the s directions so
与s方向相反，因此给出了为什么要抛出一个
an opposite to the s directions so here's the case given why if you throw a
here's the case given why if you throw a ball is blocked here so actions here be
球在这里被挡住，所以这里的动作被分开了
ball is blocked here so actions here be separated
separated if Y is not given the ball can go
如果没有给出Y，则球可以通过，如果Y，则可以从X到Z
if Y is not given the ball can go through you can go from X to Z here if Y
through you can go from X to Z here if Y is given to the spot from X Y Z is
从XYZ到该点被封锁了，所以如果您知道怪物
is given to the spot from X Y Z is blocked so if you you know the monster
blocked so if you you know the monster me back so actions here independent
我回来了，所以这里的动作基本上独立于Y我只是给你
me back so actions here independent basically given Y I'm just giving you
basically given Y I'm just giving you this you know because this is what we're
你知道这是因为如果没有给出Y我们将再次使用
this you know because this is what we're gonna use again if Y is not given then
gonna use again if Y is not given then the ball can go from X to Z no problem
球可以从X到Z没问题，这就是解释的一种方法
the ball can go from X to Z no problem and then this is the is explaining a way
and then this is the is explaining a way situation excellency the path is blocked
情况优越，如果没有观察到Y，则路径被阻塞到Y
situation excellency the path is blocked to Y if Y is not observed was very
to Y if Y is not observed was very important it's observe then you can go
重要的是要观察，然后您可以从X转到Z，所以如果您还记得那些
important it's observe then you can go from X to Z so if you remember those
from X to Z so if you remember those rules basically you can test
原则上，您可以在任何定向下降中测试独立性
rules basically you can test independence in any directed drop
independence in any directed drop without doing any calculations budget
不用做任何计算，现在我说你可以做任何事情的预算
without doing any calculations budget okay now when I say you can do any
okay now when I say you can do any calculations obviously books given with
计算显然带有135给出的书，但实际上它们给了您正确的
calculations obviously books given with 135 but actually they give you the right
135 but actually they give you the right answers right so maybe I will do a
答案正确，所以也许我会做一个简单的例子，你们可以做更多
answers right so maybe I will do a trivial example you guys can do a more
trivial example you guys can do a more complicated example but before you do an
复杂的示例，但在您进行示例之前，我还需要告诉您哦
complicated example but before you do an example I also need to tell you oh this
example I also need to tell you oh this is the same slide but you have to
是同一张幻灯片，但您必须在条件下进行确认，这样会发生什么情况
is the same slide but you have to confirm under conditions so what happens
confirm under conditions so what happens is the bone which is the root node of
是骨头，它是列表的根节点，因此有推动器
is the bone which is the root node of the list and so there are pusher to
the list and so there are pusher to boundary conditions if you reach
边界条件，如果您到达尼克节点并且观察到神话笔记
boundary conditions if you reach Nick node and the myth note is observed
Nick node and the myth note is observed the note comes back all right if this is
如果基本上观察到，便条纸会回到正确的位置，我们越多
the note comes back all right if this is observed basically the more the us the
observed basically the more the us the ball okay now if the error goes in the
现在，如果错误朝着另一个方向发展，现在可以了，那么在这种情况下，如果
ball okay now if the error goes in the other direction okay so in this case if
other direction okay so in this case if Y is different the path is blocked all
Y不同，路径被完全阻止，因此球不会返回
Y is different the path is blocked all right so the ball doesn't return back
right so the ball doesn't return back the opposite would interfere
相反会干扰，如果观察到Y，则商场
the opposite would interfere and if Y's are observed the mall
and if Y's are observed the mall compartment this way we need something
这样，我们需要一些东西来停止算法点
compartment this way we need something to have to stop the algorithm dot
to have to stop the algorithm dot something it is listed among the
当我们做一些例子时，它被列在关系中
something it is listed among the relationship when we do some examples
relationship when we do some examples remind me to come back on the slide 29
提醒我回到幻灯片29，这样您就可以看到
remind me to come back on the slide 29 so you can see that through these
so you can see that through these boundary conditions actually do make
边界条件实际上确实使教堂还不错，所以这就是我们
boundary conditions actually do make Church okay so this is what we were
Church okay so this is what we were talking on the previous slide right this
在上一张幻灯片上说的正确，这就是这种情况，所以如果Y
talking on the previous slide right this is exactly this situation here so if Y
is exactly this situation here so if Y is observable x mark if Y will observe
是可观察的x标记，如果Y将遵守模型块，那么让我们考虑
is observable x mark if Y will observe the model block so let's consider the
the model block so let's consider the following situation we have this V
下面的情况，我们有这个V结构，可以观察到
following situation we have this V structure-wise are observed all right
structure-wise are observed all right don't pay attention to this
不要注意这是观察到的墙壁，所以如果我发现
don't pay attention to this the walls are observed so if I found
the walls are observed so if I found from it what is going to happen here
从它那里会发生什么
您可以在这种情况下告诉X的em f我们绝对可以肯定的是，答案是否定的。
the walls are observed so if I found from it what is going to happen here
you can tell em f of X in this case we're more definitely the answer is no
您可以在这种情况下告诉X的em f我们绝对可以肯定的是，答案是否定的。
we're more definitely the answer is no all right this is what okay so the
好吧，这是好的，所以罂粟花吹了，但是让我们考虑一下
all right this is what okay so the poppies blow however let's consider how
poppies blow however let's consider how many K Y is not observed but let's say
没有观察到许多KY，但可以说它是Y的子代或
many K Y is not observed but let's say it's children of Y or some noise in the
it's children of Y or some noise in the presentation of eyes observe then with
眼神的表现然后观察，如果有同谋，那么宗教就是为什么
presentation of eyes observe then with if accomplice so religion is why the
if accomplice so religion is why the Magnaflow but now what you seen desired
Magnaflow，但现在您所看到的是想要的，然后在a和a重的情况下会发生什么
Magnaflow but now what you seen desired then what happens in an in a and a heavy
then what happens in an in a and a heavy disclosed sentiment analysis for y prime
公开的y情绪分析是有效y的嘈杂版本
disclosed sentiment analysis for y prime is a noisy version of Y effectively y
is a noisy version of Y effectively y prime is a noisy version of Y observing
素数是Y观测值y的嘈杂版本素数是Y观测值Y和
prime is a noisy version of Y observing y Prime's the stainless observing Y and
y Prime's the stainless observing Y and when you observed Y what confidence to
当你观察到Y对远程有什么信心
when you observed Y what confidence to remote
你记得
you remember
因此，当您观察现场直播（如果不是X投票）时，您可以达到
so when you observe live right if it's not vote for X you can reach you can
not vote for X you can reach you can reach Z okay so this is a tricky
到达Z好，这是一个棘手的情况
reach Z okay so this is a tricky situation
situation all right to you when you have this
当您进行此重组时，对您来说没什么问题，这说明了您
all right to you when you have this restructure this explaining away and you
restructure this explaining away and you have something here an observation we
这里有一些观察，我们从Y的孩子那里得到了证据
have something here an observation we have evidence from the children of Y
have evidence from the children of Y pretty effectively the same as having
实际上与对Y本身进行观察相同，因为
pretty effectively the same as having observations on Y itself because
observations on Y itself because basically this unlocks the path from X
基本上，这可以解锁从X到Z的路径，所以让我们写一下
basically this unlocks the path from X to Z all right so let's write this and
to Z all right so let's write this and see that this is not just released but
看到它不仅发布了，而且以某种方式确实有意义，所以让我们
see that this is not just released but somehow they do make sense so let's
somehow they do make sense so let's start with the most trivial case so
从最琐碎的情况开始，所以我们要唱这首好歌
start with the most trivial case so we're going to take this alright song
we're going to take this alright song writing my dissolution Direction Y and
在给定Z的XP的情况下，写出我的溶出方向Y和VST效果py
writing my dissolution Direction Y and VST effects py given X P of Z given Y
VST effects py given X P of Z given Y all right so all right so we condition
好吧，好吧，所以我们以Y为条件，如果我是Y的证据，那么接下来
all right so all right so we condition on Y so next if I am evidence of Y what
on Y so next if I am evidence of Y what happens between X and Z and I'm just
发生在X和Z之间，我只是在用分子的知识
happens between X and Z and I'm just using you know from the numerator little
using you know from the numerator little bit of XY and Z and denominator
XY和Z的位以及分母确信Y这是x和y的P
bit of XY and Z and denominator convinced of Y this is P of x and y so
convinced of Y this is P of x and y so this is no P of x given Y so you notice
在给定Y的情况下，这不是x的P，因此您会注意到卓越与
this is no P of x given Y so you notice that excellency become independent of
that excellency become independent of given Y right okay so when we have this
给定Y对，所以当我们拥有这个时，您就可以观察到它可以包含
given Y right okay so when we have this you know observed and it can contain
you know observed and it can contain here had some pain and observe then the
这里有些痛苦，观察然后路径被阻塞，那就是我们知道的
here had some pain and observe then the path is blocked and that's we you know
path is blocked and that's we you know we call this graph separation right and
我们称此图分离为对，它等效于
we call this graph separation right and it's equivalent to
it's equivalent to this independent simulation would be
这个独立的模拟将是一个无缝的问题，所以这里的想法是
this independent simulation would be seamless a question so the idea here is
seamless a question so the idea here is rather than having to prove an equation
而不是必须证明这样的等式，如果您可以证明该音符
rather than having to prove an equation like that if you can prove that the note
like that if you can prove that the note section Z are not separated all right
Z部分没有分开，箭头刻度的位置
section Z are not separated all right and the rien tation of the arrow scale
and the rien tation of the arrow scale don't even make a big difference okay
甚至不要做很大的改变好吧，他会用最大的痣
don't even make a big difference okay stretch he'll use the biggest mole
stretch he'll use the biggest mole algorithm for something from extra
零到零之间的多余部分的算法
algorithm for something from extra between zero and that part is blocked
between zero and that part is blocked then excellency are independent even why
那么卓越是独立的，即使为什么Felicia Rizal会提高到
then excellency are independent even why okay Felicia Rizal would it improve to
okay Felicia Rizal would it improve to check this permission independent spirit
查看此许可独立精神
好吧，您知道这是Michael che的第一文件夹，它说给定
okay Felicia Rizal would it improve to check this permission independent spirit
okay you know this is the Michael che all right first folder and it says given
好吧，您知道这是Michael che的第一文件夹，它说给定
all right first folder and it says given X I X I plus 1 is independent of for the
XIXI加1与上一个练习无关
X I X I plus 1 is independent of for the previous exercise right this the
previous exercise right this the first-order Markov chain can give me an
一阶马尔可夫链可以通过使用
first-order Markov chain can give me an argument of this being through using the
argument of this being through using the separation however going to stop this
分离但是要阻止这个，这就是你知道的，所以我们说
separation however going to stop this that this is you know so let's say in
that this is you know so let's say in this case x-rays the evidence for my
这个案例会为我的眼睛提供X光证据3然后我说，基本上
this case x-rays the evidence for my eyes 3 then I say that basically what we
eyes 3 then I say that basically what we need to prove is to let's say that X for
需要证明的是，在最终案文1中，假设X代表所有正确的漏洞利用
need to prove is to let's say that X for all right exploits in the final text 1
你实际上你知道的很好，所以这是正确的证据，所以我们改善了
you actually you know so okay so this is the evidence right so we improve our
the evidence right so we improve our exports in defender of x2 and x1 Topshop
x2和x1 Topshop防御者的出口，您将如何饮用这种饮料？
exports in defender of x2 and x1 Topshop are you going to drink this how you
are you going to drink this how you gonna prove that given explain that
将证明给定的解释将独立的效果导出到没有
gonna prove that given explain that exports independent effects to without
exports independent effects to without doing any calculations
做任何计算
但删除使战争发怒的算法
exports independent effects to without doing any calculations
but remove the algorithm that makes war angry
所以我们在这种情况下用箭头杀死了什么情况，不是，这是
so what situation do we have killed with the arrows in this evidence no this is
the arrows in this evidence no this is what Henson tell you all right so if you
亨森告诉你的一切都很好，所以如果你扔一个球而没有观察到树木
what Henson tell you all right so if you throw a ball look and no trees observe
throw a ball look and no trees observe what happens when you throw the ball
当您从x264的口袋里丢球时会发生什么事，所以没事吧
what happens when you throw the ball from x264 the pocket no all right so
from x264 the pocket no all right so it's sports independent XP sing with me
如果我给它加分时，这是与运动无关的XP和我一起唱歌
it's sports independent XP sing with me if I put a little extra on when it rates
if I put a little extra on when it rates extreme I want to probe in the pencil
极端，我想用X 4的铅笔探测X 1，所以如果我扔了，我们
extreme I want to probe in the pencil for X 4 for X 1 so if I throw and we're
for X 4 for X 1 so if I throw and we're from extraordinaire its X 3
来自非凡，它的X 3是，因为没有观察到该节点
from extraordinaire its X 3 yes because this node is not observe but
yes because this node is not observe but popular tax free
大众免税
好的，所以现在这个教程示例我认为您认为这是理所当然的，但是您知道
yes because this node is not observe but popular tax free
ok so now this tutorial example I think you take it for granted but you know if
好的，所以现在这个教程示例我认为您认为这是理所当然的，但是您知道
you take it for granted but you know if I start making fancy connections between
我开始在规范先生之间建立花哨的联系，这是非常简单的算法，
I start making fancy connections between the norms mister very easy algorithm to
the norms mister very easy algorithm to prove independence without having to do
证明独立性，而无需市长亲自进行任何计算
prove independence without having to do any calculations by hand and mayors
any calculations by hand and mayors against assuming to give you a platform
反对假设给你一个平台工作来做这个事情好吧，所以所有
against assuming to give you a platform work to work on this thing okay so all
work to work on this thing okay so all right an issue because it's sort of an
解决一个问题，因为这是再次执行此操作的一种重要方式
right an issue because it's sort of an important way of doing this ok again
important way of doing this ok again showing in this case with a dispatcher
在这种情况下显示的是调度员右尾并观察
showing in this case with a dispatcher right with a tail and tail and observe
好吧，不，对不起，好吧，这不是先生
okay what no I'm sorry it's okay it's not at this time sir
not at this time sir this is this is the four o'clock sir
这就是这四点钟先生的权利，失败与失败，并遵守
this is this is the four o'clock sir rights and fail and fail and observe the
rights and fail and fail and observe the path is blocked for I didn't observe the
路径被阻塞，因为我没有观察到零件被阻塞好了，所以在这种情况下
path is blocked for I didn't observe the part is unblocked okay so in this case
part is unblocked okay so in this case of the fourth given why actions they're
给出了为什么它们是独立动作的第四分之三
of the fourth given why actions they're independent
independent if why some observe that you know if in
如果为什么有人观察到您知道在这种情况下是否可以看到
if why some observe that you know if in this case you can see that the
this case you can see that the probability affection see margarine
概率影响见人造黄油基本上你知道这不等于
probability affection see margarine basically you know this is not equal to
basically you know this is not equal to P of X x gives independence
X x的P给出独立性
再次，远景，这是我最困难的案件证明书，有两个
basically you know this is not equal to P of X x gives independence
and again vistas this is the most difficult case certificate I have two
再次，远景，这是我最困难的案件证明书，有两个
difficult case certificate I have two causes of why if the part is blocked
为什么当y为空时部分被阻塞的原因是
causes of why if the part is blocked when y is nothing self that's the
when y is nothing self that's the opposite from all the previous cases if
与前面所有情况相反，如果在两个方向上都可以观察到Y，则可以行走
opposite from all the previous cases if Y is observed in the both can walk
Y is observed in the both can walk through all right
通过所有的权利
好吧，所以再次与x和z处于边际的情况相反
Y is observed in the both can walk through all right
okay so again goes to its opposite from the other case x and z are marginally
好吧，所以再次与x和z处于边际的情况相反
the other case x and z are marginally independent but you can try to establish
独立的，但您可以尝试建立基本的初始独立性
independent but you can try to establish basically initial independence given the
basically initial independence given the evidence Y X is not independent you okay
证据表明YX不是独立的，您还好，我们谈到了
evidence Y X is not independent you okay and we talked about this let's
and we talked about this let's concentrate on this on this example
专注于这个例子，他们需要什么，因为你
concentrate on this on this example right they need anything because you
right they need anything because you know I have no idea with the space here
知道我对这里的空间一无所知，因为我们需要一起思考
know I have no idea with the space here okay because we need to think together
okay because we need to think together here so you can help me as you aspiring
在这里，因此您可以在有志于在这里发言时为我提供帮助，所以在这种情况下，我可以
here so you can help me as you aspiring speaking here so in this case I have
speaking here so in this case I have nothing observed and I thought well for
没有观察到任何东西，我想的很好，接下来您能告诉我发生了什么步骤吗
nothing observed and I thought well for next can you tell me what happens step
next can you tell me what happens step by step and maybe if you don't remember
分步进行，也许如果您忘记了，我们会回到之前的所有幻灯片
by step and maybe if you don't remember we go back to all the previous slides
来自X，我想看看没有涉及的地方
from from X and I want to see where this not hasn't involved
not hasn't involved so what is my extraction phase of the
所以我的结构提取阶段是什么，所以这是
so what is my extraction phase of the structure all right so this is
structure all right so this is unobserved alright so what happens to
没观察到好，所以两者发生的事情在路径上看起来都很紧张
unobserved alright so what happens to the both look nervous to the to the path
the both look nervous to the to the path here when I look at the two arrows being
在这里，当我看着像这样向下的两个箭头时
here when I look at the two arrows being down like that
我可以从X移到Y否，因为观察到的情况我可以从X移到W
can I go from X to Y no because those are observed can I move over from X to W
我可以从X转到W是吗，因为太太。根据观察到的生活的斯泰森故事是
can I go from X to W yeah because mrs. Stetson tale based on observed life is
Stetson tale based on observed life is Pakistan block okay then I mixed loudly
巴基斯坦封锁好了，然后我大声混音，音量下降到什么水平
Pakistan block okay then I mixed loudly and what happens to the volume down to
and what happens to the volume down to you when that me is not observed goes up
当你没有观察到我的时候你会上升，所以球丢了，他们再也不会回来
you when that me is not observed goes up so the ball is lost they never come back
so the ball is lost they never come back okay tell me now what happens when I
好吧，现在告诉我，当我观察到你的时候会发生什么
okay tell me now what happens when I observed that me you
observed that me you so obviously the volume there all right
所以很明显那里的音量很好，你知道我们什么也没说
so obviously the volume there all right you know we don't say anything
you know we don't say anything stimulus situation so the ball comes
刺激的情况，所以球来了好了，从零开始会发生什么
stimulus situation so the ball comes here okay what happens this from zero
here okay what happens this from zero from our bounding conditions the mall
从我们的边界条件来看，购物中心回来了，然后观察到
from our bounding conditions the mall comes back and then this one observed
comes back and then this one observed the wall was too wide to here
墙太宽了，在这里给定W，关于x和y我们能说什么
the wall was too wide to here what can we say about x and y given W
所以我们有这个RR是分隔的x和y，并且两个列表都可以达到Y
so we have this RR is the x and y in the separated and both the list can reach Y
separated and both the list can reach Y so what can you tell me when that B is
所以你能告诉我什么时候观察到B，以便明年
so what can you tell me when that B is observed so in order for next year it's
observed so in order for next year it's Y all right so this is the Ritz ability
是的，所以这是丽兹能力条件，所以烦人的W或多或少
Y all right so this is the Ritz ability condition so annoying W is more or less
condition so annoying W is more or less the same as knowing easy and you can
就像了解简单一样，您可以从析构函数中记住
the same as knowing easy and you can remember from the destructor
remember from the destructor knowing this the evidence makes notes x
知道这一证据后，便会记录x和y，从而使它们具有从属权利
knowing this the evidence makes notes x and y what makes them dependent right
and y what makes them dependent right because anything we say about X or Y
因为我们所说的关于X或Y的任何内容都暗示着关于瑜伽的某些知识
because anything we say about X or Y imply something about yoga okay
imply something about yoga okay all right so here the take apart is any
好的，所以这里值得一提的是您从中获得的任何信息
all right so here the take apart is any information that you get down from
information that you get down from chamber is basically four five eighths
分庭基本上是四个五分之八点半，这是棘手的部分
chamber is basically four five eighths half points and this is the tricky part
half points and this is the tricky part for this graphs
对于这个图
我知道，但是这个想法是对的，我们正尝试让您知道有趣的时候
half points and this is the tricky part for this graphs
I know but the idea is right we're trying to see you know when interesting
我知道，但是这个想法是对的，我们正尝试让您知道有趣的时候
trying to see you know when interesting to go back from X to X right there is
从X返回X的右边，你知道我们要坚持它的
to go back from X to X right there is you know we want to stick its the
you know we want to stick its the volcano rich wife Theresa part ever
火山富婆特蕾莎（Theresa part）永远没有粉红猪小妹（Peppa）好吗
volcano rich wife Theresa part ever no Peppa okay
如果您的目标保持不变，这是您阅读的一个示例，这是
this is an example that you read if your target stays the same things and this is
target stays the same things and this is a very nice example from Bishop's book
Bishop的书中的一个非常好的例子，实际上是关于
a very nice example from Bishop's book actually about buzzes compilations for
actually about buzzes compilations for this explaining away paste okay so I
这个解释消失了，好吧，所以我记得我遍历了所有答案文胸
this explaining away paste okay so I remember I go through all the answer bra
remember I go through all the answer bra and I believe I'm not sure but I think
我相信我不确定，但我认为他们以前的Chrome作品之一
and I believe I'm not sure but I think one of their former chrome works has
one of their former chrome works has this something like this okay so there
这样的事情还可以，所以以前有个问题，但是肯定可以
this something like this okay so there is a former problem but so certainly do
is a former problem but so certainly do this homework and when we see the
这个作业，当我们看到代数代数时，他们在这里说
this homework and when we see the algebra algebra they say here in wrote
algebra algebra they say here in wrote you've got zero point 1 1 1 then 0 1 1 1
您得到零点1 1 1然后是0 1 1 1，因为您会感激不尽
you've got zero point 1 1 1 then 0 1 1 1 because you will appreciate
because you will appreciate but this numbers is not magic right
但是这个数字不是魔术，基本上不会因此而变得
but this numbers is not magic right there's not become basically by this
there's not become basically by this condition of of abilities that we assume
能力的条件，我们假设它们是已知的，并且这个先验还可以，所以当
condition of of abilities that we assume them known and this prior okay so when
them known and this prior okay so when you do this algebra so in this case it's
你做这个代数，所以在这种情况下，基本上是相同的例子
you do this algebra so in this case it's basically to the same example that we
basically to the same example that we will discuss in with the rain case
将会与下雨情况进行讨论，所以知道这是0
will discuss in with the rain case alright so knowing that this is 0
alright so knowing that this is 0 somehow saying something about B
以某种方式说出有关B的信息会产生这种可能性
somehow saying something about B produces the probability that this left
produces the probability that this left is 0 all right since we explained the
是0，因为我们解释了我从Z收到的观察
is 0 all right since we explained the observation that I receive from Z this
observation that I receive from Z this is a very nice example please
这是一个很好的例子，请缠绕并进行计算
is a very nice example please winded and do that calculation okay
你能用最大的米兰作品告诉我，他们甚至有权利像我一样吗？
can you show me with the biggest Milan written that they even have right as my
written that they even have right as my evidence is independent of B given a
证据独立于B，告诉我您将如何处理
evidence is independent of B given a tell me what you will do with the
tell me what you will do with the biggest ball algorithm
最大球算法
太可怕了，我跌倒了我无法达到的规则，如果这是真的，那么先生。
tell me what you will do with the biggest ball algorithm
so terrible I fell beyond the rules can I reach and if this is true right mr.
太可怕了，我跌倒了我无法达到的规则，如果这是真的，那么先生。
I reach and if this is true right mr. Sanford the ball is blocked right so no
Sanford球被挡住了，所以没有迫不及待，因为我们相信我们不能
Sanford the ball is blocked right so no no wait because we believe we cannot
no wait because we believe we cannot think it's like eating and blind being
认为这就像吃饭和瞎子对吧哦，当您检查手机时
think it's like eating and blind being right Oh checking your phone when you
right Oh checking your phone when you walk and then you expect me to pay
走，然后你希望我也对你注意同一件事
walk and then you expect me to pay attention to you right the same thing
attention to you right the same thing so a independent big given up you know
所以一个独立的大人物放弃了，你知道告诉我有关球的事情，所以我喜欢
so a independent big given up you know tell me about the ball so I like the
tell me about the ball so I like the ball I say if I bought from a what
我说如果我从一个球上买到它来时发生了什么，那么我会说
ball I say if I bought from a what happens to it when it comes here then
happens to it when it comes here then the whole roll up left alright so the
整个卷起都向左行，这样电动机就被向右堵住了，因为
the whole roll up left alright so the motor is blocked right right because
motor is blocked right right because this is unobserved okay so this part is
这是无法观察的，所以这部分被阻止了，但是无论如何我们都验证不是
this is unobserved okay so this part is blocked but anyways we verify was not
blocked but anyways we verify was not the case and then one goes up there
的情况，然后一个人在那里，因为这要观察这一部分将
the case and then one goes up there because this to observe this part will
because this to observe this part will also be blocked right so you know but
也被封锁了，所以你知道但不在那里
also be blocked right so you know but not there
好吧，这是相同的语言或完全相同的不同水域
okay this is sort of the same language or different waters exactly the same
or different waters exactly the same thing okay these are all the rules
好的，这些都是规则
现在您可能会问我为什么幻灯片不流动，因为您有时知道
or different waters exactly the same thing okay these are all the rules
now you may ask me why are the slides not liquid because you know sometimes I
现在您可能会问我为什么幻灯片不流动，因为您有时知道
not liquid because you know sometimes I in here let's say 2005 I ride the slide
在这里，假设2005年我骑滑梯而我忘了，那么你有2015年
in here let's say 2005 I ride the slide and that I forgot and then you have 2015
and that I forgot and then you have 2015 I prefer something else and and then you
我更喜欢别的东西，然后你得到它没什么，这很好，但是你知道
I prefer something else and and then you get it's nothing it's nice but you know
get it's nothing it's nice but you know what I like to keep that because when
我喜欢保留的内容是因为当您阅读它们时，您会多放一页
what I like to keep that because when you read them yes you put an extra page
you read them yes you put an extra page but you may get something from the
但您可能会从另一张幻灯片中得到一些东西，似乎是
but you may get something from the different slide that seems to be the
different slide that seems to be the same but may have something different
一样，但那里可能有所不同
same but may have something different there okay
不要生气，所以在我们之前有一个简单的例子
don't be pissed so some simple example just before we
so some simple example just before we finish the election today right we
今天就完成选举，我们真的必须接受这个
finish the election today right we really have to take this
really have to take this so this is the proportion if you collect
因此，如果您很少从iid数据中收集数据，那么这就是比例
so this is the proportion if you collect data from iid data with little
data from iid data with little innovation and something new what can be
创新和新事物可能是其他事物，实际上这可能是
innovation and something new what can be something else actually this can be an
something else actually this can be an indicator variables no tells you what
指标变量no告诉您这里的混合中是什么高斯，但是
indicator variables no tells you what Gaussian in a mixture here's but the
Gaussian in a mixture here's but the idea here is would you look at the
这里的想法是你要看看数据的概率，所以所有这些
idea here is would you look at the probability of the data so these all the
probability of the data so these all the collections of data x1 to xn each of
数据x1至xn的收集这些给您的消费税是
collections of data x1 to xn each of these the excise given you is
these the excise given you is independent alright so this is the iid
独立好吧，所以这是你们在每个
independent alright so this is the iid assumption that you guys use in every
assumption that you guys use in every statistics course you pay and the idea
您支付的统计课程，这里的想法是图形表示
statistics course you pay and the idea here is representation a graphical
here is representation a graphical representation of the I I need property
II需求属性的表示形式是带有城市的简单图形，因此可以
representation of the I I need property is the simple graph with the city so can
is the simple graph with the city so can somebody tell me just you know why this
有人告诉我，你知道为什么这张图基本上发明了这种独立性
somebody tell me just you know why this graph basically invent this independence
graph basically invent this independence relation otherwise my x1 is independent
关系，否则我的x1独立于X 2
relation otherwise my x1 is independent of X 2
在这种情况下，从x1转到x2的唯一方法是向右的虚线箭头
what is the only way to go from x1 to x2 in this case the broken arrow right
所以等等我什么时候得到这个
so wait when do I get this
所以不要害怕过山车，因为我的exe是我的约会对象，显然
so don't get coaster scared okay because my exes are my date obviously have to
my exes are my date obviously have to mark them because that's my evidence
标记它们，因为那是我的证据，但是当我写此关系时，
mark them because that's my evidence right but when I write this relation and
right but when I write this relation and I'm looking at this Malaysian my
我正在从公开演讲中看到这个马来西亚人的证据是什么
I'm looking at this Malaysian my evidence from public speakings what
evidence from public speakings what right you know what variable when I say
对，当我说给定的三个月亮时，你知道什么变量，所以如果我
right you know what variable when I say three of the given moon right so if I
three of the given moon right so if I want to welcome x1 to x2 I have to go
要欢迎x1到x2，我必须仔细检查新证据，所以我已经
want to welcome x1 to x2 I have to go through the evidence new alright so I've
through the evidence new alright so I've got another 2x2 the path from here is
又得到了2x2，从这里开始的路径被封锁了
got another 2x2 the path from here is blocked all right
blocked all right because I already know the values of me
因为我已经知道我的价值观，所以您需要开始多年
because I already know the values of me okay so you need to start get years to
okay so you need to start get years to do this little drops basically that
做这些小滴，基本上是因为他们不只是一种假医生
do this little drops basically that they're not just a sort of dummy doctor
they're not just a sort of dummy doctor relations but they embed from holistic
关系，但它们是从整体关系中嵌入的，所以本质上讲，当您拥有
relations but they embed from holistic relationship so in essence when you have
relationship so in essence when you have this graph immediately this is their
这张图立刻是他们的权利，所以它一次都不是另一个
this graph immediately this is their right so it's not one of the other once
right so it's not one of the other once you plot it this is what immediately you
您将其绘制出来，这就是您立即暗示您拥有iid的原因
you plot it this is what immediately you are implying that you have the iid
are implying that you have the iid assumption
假设还可以，你显然可以知道
assumption okay and you can obviously you know hear
okay and you can obviously you know hear that if you might analyze me out all
如果你可以对我进行分析
that if you might analyze me out all right
right that marginally basically you can P of
基本上你可以成为我的P
that marginally basically you can P of me
me it doesn't factor is P of X 1 P of X 2
它不考虑X的P 1或X 2的P等，所以没有真正的
it doesn't factor is P of X 1 P of X 2 etc okay and so there's no really
etc okay and so there's no really all right the basically you cannot you
好吧，基本上，你不能，你不能批准任何独立性，所以让我们
all right the basically you cannot you cannot approve any independence so let's
cannot approve any independence so let's do
做
再次请那些琐碎的例子之一，让我们来证明这一切
cannot approve any independence so let's do
so again please maybe one of those trivial example so let's prove this all
再次请那些琐碎的例子之一，让我们来证明这一切
trivial example so let's prove this all right so we have evidence x2 and we want
对，所以我们有证据x2，我们想证明两个不同的X
right so we have evidence x2 and we want to prove that X for two different
to prove that X for two different effects on an extinct
会影响灭绝，所以请原谅我想要的红色Nestor
effects on an extinct okay so excuse my red Nestor we want to
okay so excuse my red Nestor we want to say exports in the final factoid exit so
说出口在最终的拟人出口中，所以使用最大的Mall算法，而不是
say exports in the final factoid exit so with the biggest mall algorithm rather
with the biggest mall algorithm rather than going to do
而不是去做所有的事情，所以给定X，我们仍然需要
than going to do all right so given X still we need to
all right so given X still we need to prove those exports in the panel of X 1
在X 1和X 6面板中证明这些出口，所以我们不要错过X 1证明
prove those exports in the panel of X 1 and X 6 so let's not miss X 1 the proof
and X 6 so let's not miss X 1 the proof independence of export X 1 where your
出口X 1的独立性，您在男孩中的角色可以通过这种方式进行，或者
independence of export X 1 where your own role in the boy can go this way or
own role in the boy can go this way or can go all the way like that so if the
可以像这样一直走下去，所以如果球这样走下去，这里发生了什么
can go all the way like that so if the ball goes this way what happens here
ball goes this way what happens here you know if the world goes this way then
你知道世界是不是这样，所以你知道是的是的
you know if the world goes this way then you know yes yes yes
好吧，你告诉我那里发生了什么
well you tell me what happens there
所以我可以从X个小鸡那里去吗我可以到x2
so can I go from X chicks can I go to x2
这样我们就可以知道了
so we can know okay
但请记住下一段文字是我说的不匹配先生的方式
but remember next text is the way that I say is a mismatch sir
say is a mismatch sir all right so it's not observed it's not
好吧，所以它没有被观察到，它是不可观察的错过
all right so it's not observed it's not observable missed
如果没有x6观察会发生什么，那就不好了，然后从X到X是正确的
if x6 is no observe what happens it's no okay and then from X to X is right this
okay and then from X to X is right this is given and and then I'm working on
被给定，然后我就以这种方式工作，然后就知道了
is given and and then I'm working on this way and then it's you know
this way and then it's you know protected too so this is true so you
也受保护，所以这是真的，所以您知道是否要写这种
protected too so this is true so you know if you write to this sort of this
know if you write to this sort of this calculation with the factorization of
用概率分布的因式分解进行计算
calculation with the factorization of the probability distribution it will
the probability distribution it will take you basically half an hour or
基本上要花你半个小时左右
take you basically half an hour or something
something if you dress this relationship you do
如果你打扮这种关系，你做的话，他们可能会因此而迷失，而不必
if you dress this relationship you do they may be lost by it you don't have to
they may be lost by it you don't have to bother again so let's finish so X 1
再次打扰，让我们结束，以便X 1给X诊所中的指数
bother again so let's finish so X 1 given X clinics the exponents in the
given X clinics the exponents in the benefit sticks okay so it's no exponents
好处棒好了，所以在没有固定时间的时候就没有指数了。有两个部分
benefit sticks okay so it's no exponents in the time no fixed is there two parts
in the time no fixed is there two parts one part is this way is this parking lot
一部分是这种方式，这是停车场，现在是这部分，是，不在这里
one part is this way is this parking lot yes right now is this part yes not here
yes right now is this part yes not here it states that given X for Linux state
它指出对于Linux，给定的X状态x2不是独立的极端，因此给定的X
it states that given X for Linux state x2 is not independent extreme so given X
x2 is not independent extreme so given X 1 X 6 roll it a little more like this
1 X 6像这样滚动一点，越能分散注意力
1 X 6 roll it a little more like this the more can walk from this distraction
the more can walk from this distraction why because this is observed then the
为什么，因为观察到了这一点，所以更多的可以去解释
why because this is observed then the more can go there can go to explain
more can go there can go to explain there is a path so this going the
有一条路，所以这倒退了
there is a path so this going the backwards
backwards okay
好的，所以这是必须要了解的最大的模型操作
all right so this is the biggest model thing in action for a must know
thing in action for a must know computation problems okay
计算问题好吧，我只完成144，所以我不
computation problems okay let me just finish what's 144 so I don't
let me just finish what's 144 so I don't know what's my last slide because I had
知道我的最后一张幻灯片是什么，因为我有，我们将从头再来
know what's my last slide because I had and we're going to come back from on
and we're going to come back from on this would do the slides on Thursday but
这会在星期四做幻灯片，但是我基本上总结了相同的内容
this would do the slides on Thursday but I went basically to summarize the same
I went basically to summarize the same slide that had before for now in
除了这个当地北部和以前的滑梯
slide that had before for now in addition to this local the northern and
addition to this local the northern and lack of property I also put this
缺乏财产我也把这个减速财产好了，你知道
lack of property I also put this deceleration property okay you know
deceleration property okay you know which is you know sort of a graph
您知道这是一种将一组图分离的图论方法
which is you know sort of a graph theoretic way of separating a set of
theoretic way of separating a set of notes a from beginner so main evidence
注意到一个初学者，所以如果我扔了这个，主要的证据可以说
notes a from beginner so main evidence shall any the say if I throw this
shall any the say if I throw this property this global map of property
财产这是财产生态学的全球地图，这是由
property this global map of property ecology this is an ahkam directed by the
ecology this is an ahkam directed by the profit division is the order Markov
利润除法是订单的马尔可夫性质，如果您可以解决下一个G
profit division is the order Markov property and if you can solve the G next
property and if you can solve the G next 12 leads to old and then you can
12导致陈旧，然后您实际上可以显示相反的结果，而不是
12 leads to old and then you can actually show the opposite which is not
actually show the opposite which is not trivial but only 12 Nick stingy all of
琐碎，但只有12个尼克小气，如果可以的话，它们都比较好
trivial but only 12 Nick stingy all of them relatively well if you could put
them relatively well if you could put one you can write the other two okay and
一个你可以写另外两个还可以，你也可以基本上解决家禽问题
one you can write the other two okay and also you can solve the poultry basically
also you can solve the poultry basically lead to the same factorization of the
导致联合分布的相同因式分解，该图是
lead to the same factorization of the Joint Distribution the graph which is
Joint Distribution the graph which is the relation that you share the body
你分享身体的关系还好，所以你知道
the relation that you share the body okay so this sort of is you know
okay so this sort of is you know something easy to remember this is way
一些容易记住的方法基本上更强大，因为
something easy to remember this is way more powerful basically because in
more powerful basically because in essence doesn't really even care what
本质上根本不关心非后代将什么倒置
essence doesn't really even care what are the non descendants invert the
are the non descendants invert the direction of the arrow says although the
箭头的方向说，尽管
direction of the arrow says although the numbering of the
numbering of the right so this made separation actually
是的，所以这种分离实际上可以应用于有向和有向
right so this made separation actually can be applied to both directed and
can be applied to both directed and undirected graphs and it is the way to
无向图，这是证明条件独立性的方法
undirected graphs and it is the way to prove condition independence to this
prove condition independence to this again if you want the top of each of
再次，如果您想要每个这些的顶部，我们正在学习这个，您有
again if you want the top of each of these we're learning this this you have
these we're learning this this you have shown them at least with examples the
至少通过示例向他们展示了事实真相很少，而您又
shown them at least with examples the truth is very few lines and again you
truth is very few lines and again you can consult one of the Bible's in in
可以在社区图形模型中查阅圣经中的其中一项
can consult one of the Bible's in in community graphical models for people
community graphical models for people okay 1:46 we will come back and and
好吧1:46我们将回来，再看三张幻灯片，然后讨论
okay 1:46 we will come back and and three some slides and then discuss about
three some slides and then discuss about the elimination algorithm when we return
我们星期四返回时的消除算法
the elimination algorithm when we return on Thursday